Anton's favourite geometric figures are regular polyhedrons. Note that there are five kinds of regular polyhedrons:

Tetrahedron. Tetrahedron has 4 triangular faces.
Cube. Cube has 6 square faces.
Octahedron. Octahedron has 8 triangular faces.
Dodecahedron. Dodecahedron has 12 pentagonal faces.
Icosahedron. Icosahedron has 20 triangular faces.
All five kinds of polyhedrons are shown on the picture below:


Anton has a collection of n polyhedrons. One day he decided to know, how many faces his polyhedrons have in total. Help Anton and find this number!

Input
The first line of the input contains a single integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 200 000) — the number of polyhedrons in Anton's collection.

Each of the following n lines of the input contains a string si — the name of the i-th polyhedron in Anton's collection. The string can look like this:

"Tetrahedron" (without quotes), if the i-th polyhedron in Anton's collection is a tetrahedron.
"Cube" (without quotes), if the i-th polyhedron in Anton's collection is a cube.
"Octahedron" (without quotes), if the i-th polyhedron in Anton's collection is an octahedron.
"Dodecahedron" (without quotes), if the i-th polyhedron in Anton's collection is a dodecahedron.
"Icosahedron" (without quotes), if the i-th polyhedron in Anton's collection is an icosahedron.
Output
Output one number — the total number of faces in all the polyhedrons in Anton's collection.

-----------------------------------------------------------------

Have an array which contains the number of faces of each polyhedra and then print the sum.