Little Chris knows there's no fun in playing dominoes, he thinks it's too random and doesn't require skill. 
Instead, he decided to play with the dominoes and make a "domino show".

Chris arranges n dominoes in a line, placing each piece vertically upright. 
In the beginning, he simultaneously pushes some of the dominoes either to the left or to the right. 
However, somewhere between every two dominoes pushed in the same direction there is at least one domino pushed in the opposite direction.

After each second, each domino that is falling to the left pushes the adjacent domino on the left. 
Similarly, the dominoes falling to the right push their adjacent dominoes standing on the right. 
When a vertical domino has dominoes falling on it from both sides, it stays still due to the balance of the forces. The figure shows one possible example of the process.


Given the initial directions Chris has pushed the dominoes, find the number of the dominoes left standing vertically at the end of the process!

Input
The first line contains a single integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 3000), the number of the dominoes in the line. The next line contains a character string s of length n. 
The i-th character of the string si is equal to

"L", if the i-th domino has been pushed to the left;
"R", if the i-th domino has been pushed to the right;
".", if the i-th domino has not been pushed.
It is guaranteed that if si = sj = "L" and i < j, then there exists such k that i < k < j and sk = "R"; 
if si = sj = "R" and i < j, then there exists such k that i < k < j and sk = "L".

Output
Output a single integer, the number of the dominoes that remain vertical at the end of the process.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Examples
input
14
.L.R...LR..L..
output
4
input
5
R....
output
0
input
1
.
output
1
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We know that there are no two consecutive pushes of one kind.

1. As we go through the domino line from the first domino, every '.' is counted as a standing domino.
2. If the character in front of a '.' is L, then every domino before it falls. So, the number of standing dominos is reset to 0.

3. If we find a 'R' at D(i), then we keep going ahead till we find either a 'L' at D(j) or the end of the string at j.
			If there are an odd number of dominos in between position i and j, then one domino stands.
			If there are an even number of dominos in between position i and j, they all fall.

			So, if {D(j) = 'R' and (j-i-1) is odd}, no_of_dominos++. 
			{-1 because we are counting the number of dominos in between i and j, exclusive. j not counted}

			i is then updated to j,

4.If we find a 'L', at D(i) then we keep going ahead till we find either a 'R' at D(j) or the end of the string at position j. 
			In either case, all the dominos from i+1 to j-1 stand.
			no_of_standing_dominos = no_of_standing_dominos + (j - i - 1) {-1 because the j-th domino doesn't stand}

			i is then updated to j.

After the dots at the beginning i.e. after the first time D(i) is an alphabet,
 i will always be either an alphabet or the end of the string. 
This is why we can afford to increment the no of standing dominos every time D(i) is a '.' 