Petya studies in a school and he adores Maths. His class has been studying arithmetic expressions. 
On the last class the teacher wrote three positive integers a, b, c on the blackboard. 
The task was to insert signs of operations '+' and '*', and probably brackets between the numbers so that the value of the resulting expression is as large as possible. 
Let's consider an example: assume that the teacher wrote numbers 1, 2 and 3 on the blackboard. Here are some ways of placing signs and brackets:

1+2*3=7
1*(2+3)=5
1*2*3=6
(1+2)*3=9
Note that you can insert operation signs only between a and b, and between b and c, that is, you cannot swap integers. 
For instance, in the given sample you cannot get expression (1+3)*2.

It's easy to see that the maximum value that you can obtain is 9.

Your task is: given a, b and c print the maximum value that you can get.

Input
The input contains three integers a, b and c, each on a single line (1 ≤ a, b, c ≤ 10).

Output
Print the maximum value of the expression that you can obtain.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Well, there are some candidate solutions - {a*b*c, (a*b)+c, a*(b+c), a+(b*c), (a+b)*c, a+b+c}
Find the maximum of these solutions.