Some days ago, I learned the concept of LCM (least common multiple). I've played with it for several times and I want to make a big number with it.

But I also don't want to use many numbers, so I'll choose three positive integers (they don't have to be distinct) which are not greater than n. Can you help me to find the maximum possible least common multiple of these three integers?

Input
The first line contains an integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 106) — the n mentioned in the statement.

Output
Print a single integer — the maximum possible LCM of three not necessarily distinct positive integers that are not greater than n.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This problem is nice.

Let a = p_1^{a_1}p_2^{a_2}...p_n^{a_n} in it's prime factorisation
    b = q_1^{b_1}q_2^{b_2}...q_m^{b_m}

Now, consider the following multisets - 

A = {p_1, p_1, ... p_1 (a_1 times), p_2, p_2 ... p_2 (a_2 times) ... p_n, p_n, ..., p_n (a_n times) }
B = {q_1, q_1, ... q_1 (b_1 times), q_2, q_2 ... q_2 (b_2 times) ... p_m, p_m, ..., q_m (b_m times) }

Then, LCM of a and b is prod(A union B). i.e. all the common prime factors (A intersection B) are crossed out once and the remaining numbers are multiplied.

More concisely, lcm(a,b)gcd(a,b) = ab

So, the lcm(a,b) <= ab, with equality holding if both numbers are coprime.

So, to solve this problem we look for the three greatest numbers that are coprime to each other.

First, the following observation - gcd(n, n+1) = gcd(n, 1) = 1, i.e. any two consecutive numbers are prime.

Three Cases - 

Case 1 : N is odd. 
Then the greatest LCM is n(n-1)(n-2).
n and n-1 are coprime as are (n-1) and n-2 because they are consecutive numbers.
n and n-2 are coprime because they are consecutive odd numbers. gcd(n, n-2) = gcd(n,2) = 1
So, the three greatest coprime numbers are guaranteed to have the greatest LCM. We are done.

Case 2 : N is even but not a multiple of 3.
Then, in that case, the greatest LCM is n(n-1)(n-3).
n and n-1 are coprime because of being consecutive numbers and n-1 and n-3 are coprime because they are consecutive odd numbers. 
gcd(n, n-3) = gcd(n,3) = 1 [Since, n is not a multiple of 3]

Note that n and n-2 are both even so not coprime.

Among the two candidate choices here - n(n-1)(n-3) and (n-1)(n-2)(n-3), the former product is greater, because n > n-2

Case 3 : N is even and a multiple of 3
Then, the greatest LCM is (n-1)(n-2)(n-3). If n is even, then n-1 is odd, and the three numbers are all coprime by virtue of being reduced to the first case.
If we wish to keep n(n-1) and search for the largest number coprime to both of them, then we cannot get a number greater than n-5.

Among (n-1)(n-2)(n-3) and n(n-1)(n-5), the former is always greater. So, we have an answer straight away.

I got an overflow error in C. 