Let's consider a table consisting of n rows and n columns. The cell located at the intersection of i-th row and j-th column contains number i × j. 
The rows and columns are numbered starting from 1.

You are given a positive integer x. Your task is to count the number of cells in a table that contain number x.

Input
The single line contains numbers n and x (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^5, 1 ≤ x ≤ 10^9) — the size of the table and the number that we are looking for in the table.

Output
Print a single number: the number of times x occurs in the table.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The question is equivalent to asking how many ordered pairs (i,j) exist such that i*j = x and i, j <= n.

We iterate i from 1 till sqrt(x) as long as i is less than n, 
			Check if x is a multiple of i. If it is, check if x/i <= n {Otherwise, the box (i, x/i) doesn't exist on the table}
							If it does exist, then increment the number of boxes by 2. { (i, x/i) and (x/i, i)}

			Lastly, when the condition i*i < x, no longer holds,
					Check if i*i = x, and if i <= n,
							If yes, increment the number of boxes by 1 because this corresponds to a single box (i,i).