"Contestant who earns a score equal to or greater than the k-th place finisher's score will advance to the next round, as long as the contestant earns a positive score..." 
— an excerpt from contest rules.

A total of n participants took part in the contest (n ≥ k), and you already know their scores. Calculate how many participants will advance to the next round.

Input
The first line of the input contains two integers n and k (1 ≤ k ≤ n ≤ 50) separated by a single space.

The second line contains n space-separated integers a1, a2, ..., an (0 ≤ ai ≤ 100), where ai is the score earned by the participant who got the i-th place. 
The given sequence is non-increasing (that is, for all i from 1 to n - 1 the following condition is fulfilled: ai ≥ ai + 1).

Output
Output the number of participants who advance to the next round.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If a_k is positive, then search for the largest i, such that a_i = a_k. The number of winners is i.

If a_k is not positive, then search for the smallest i, such that a_i is positive. The number of winners is i.

Since, the array is already sorted, these searches are very easy.