You are a lover of bacteria. You want to raise some bacteria in a box.

Initially, the box is empty. Each morning, you can put any number of bacteria into the box. 
And each night, every bacterium in the box will split into two bacteria. You hope to see exactly x bacteria in the box at some moment.

What is the minimum number of bacteria you need to put into the box across those days?

Input
The only line containing one integer x (1 ≤ x ≤ 109).

Output
The only line containing one integer: the answer.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Very surprisingly, the answer is the number of 1s in the binary representation of a number !

If a number l = b_n 2^n + b_{n-1} 2^{n-1} + ... + (b_1) 2 + b_0, where b_0 ... b_n are the binary digits of l and can be either 0 or 1. 

If we put a bacteria on day 1, there will be 2^n bacteria after n days.
If we put a bacteria on day 5 as well, there will be 2^{n-1} + 2^{n-5}

So, if a number is 2^a + 2^b + 2^c + ...., we accordingly put bacteria on those days. So, there is a bijection in between the number of bacteria and 1s in it's binary 
representation.

An algorithm has to be used to find the number of 1s in a 64 bit number. I already wrote a program to find 'population count' of a number in the Mathematical Stuff repository. 