Mr. Funt now lives in a country with a very specific tax laws. The total income of mr. Funt during this year is equal to n (n ≥ 2) burles and the amount of tax 
he has to pay is calculated as the maximum divisor of n (not equal to n, of course). 
For example, if n = 6 then Funt has to pay 3 burles, while for n = 25 he needs to pay 5 and if n = 2 he pays only 1 burle.

As mr. Funt is a very opportunistic person he wants to cheat a bit. In particular, he wants to split the initial n in several parts n1 + n2 + ... + nk = n 
(here k is arbitrary, even k = 1 is allowed) and pay the taxes for each part separately. He can't make some part equal to 1 because it will reveal him. 
So, the condition ni ≥ 2 should hold for all i from 1 to k.

Ostap Bender wonders, how many money Funt has to pay (i.e. minimal) if he chooses and optimal way to split n in parts.

Input
The first line of the input contains a single integer n (2 ≤ n ≤ 2·109) — the total year income of mr. Funt.

Output
Print one integer — minimum possible number of burles that mr. Funt has to pay as a tax.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

I saw the connection with the Goldbach conjecture but couldn't see how it was possible to do this. 

But, this problem rests on the fact that the conjecture has already been numerically verified within the bounds specified in the problem. So, it may be treated like a 
theorem within this range.

Case 1 : n is prime
If the number is prime, then only 1 has to be paid. That is the minimum possible amount to be paid.

Case 2 : n is even and not prime (not = 2)
The next minimum is 2.
Since the Goldbach conjecture has been verified upto the limit, we can use it. Any even number is the sum of two primes.
We don't need to actually find the pair of primes, we just know it exists. 
If a number is even and not 2, the tax payable is 2.
 
Case 3 : n is odd and composite but (n-2) is prime -

If a number is odd and composite , n = (n-2) + 2, is the only way it can be written as the sum of two primes. 2 is the only even prime number.
The sum of two odd numbers is another odd number. So, an even number has to be involved in the sum. If (n-2) is prime, then the minimum tax = 1+1 = 2

Case 4 : n is odd and composite and (n -2) is composite - 
n = n-3 + 3, and then n-3 is an even number and has minimum return 2. 3 is prime. 2+1 = 3. This is the maximum possible tax that will ever be given
following the scheme. 

Note - The primality test can be done in O(root(n))