A tennis tournament with n participants is running. The participants are playing by an olympic system, so the winners move on and the losers drop out.

The tournament takes place in the following way (below, m is the number of the participants of the current round):

let k be the maximal power of the number 2 such that k ≤ m,
k participants compete in the current round and a half of them passes to the next round, the other m - k participants pass to the next round directly,
when only one participant remains, the tournament finishes.
Each match requires b bottles of water for each participant and one bottle for the judge. Besides p towels are given to each participant for the whole tournament.

Find the number of bottles and towels needed for the tournament.

Note that it's a tennis tournament so in each match two participants compete (one of them will win and the other will lose).

Input
The only line contains three integers n, b, p (1 ≤ n, b, p ≤ 500) — the number of participants and the parameters described in the problem statement.

Output
Print two integers x and y — the number of bottles and towels need for the tournament.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The number of matches can be counted through a simple bijection with the number of eliminations. One match leads to one elimination, and one elimination necissarily.

If there are n people, then there have to be n-1 matches. We need n-1 eliminations to end.

No of bottles = no of matches*(2b + 1)
No of towels = no of participants*p