There are n walruses sitting in a circle. All of them are numbered in the clockwise order: the walrus number 2 sits to the left of the walrus number 1, the walrus number 3 sits to the left of the walrus number 2, ..., the walrus number 1 sits to the left of the walrus number n.

The presenter has m chips. The presenter stands in the middle of the circle and starts giving the chips to the walruses starting from walrus number 1 and moving clockwise. The walrus number i gets i chips. If the presenter can't give the current walrus the required number of chips, then the presenter takes the remaining chips and the process ends. Determine by the given n and m how many chips the presenter will get in the end.

Input
The first line contains two integers n and m (1 ≤ n ≤ 50, 1 ≤ m ≤ 104) — the number of walruses and the number of chips correspondingly.

Output
Print the number of chips the presenter ended up with.

-----------------------------------------------------------

Very simple. Just go around the circle. We need simple modular arithmetic.

Start at walrus i = 1. And then go to walrus (i%no_of_walruses)+1.

The residue class of n goes from 0 to n-1. But, we are counting from 1 to n. So, we add n.