The new "Die Hard" movie has just been released! There are n people at the cinema box office standing in a huge line. 
Each of them has a single 100, 50 or 25 ruble bill. A "Die Hard" ticket costs 25 rubles. 
Can the booking clerk sell a ticket to each person and give the change if he initially has no money and sells the tickets strictly in the order people follow in the line?

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 105) — the number of people in the line.
 The next line contains n integers, each of them equals 25, 50 or 100 — the values of the bills the people have.
 The numbers are given in the order from the beginning of the line (at the box office) to the end of the line.

Output
Print "YES" (without the quotes) if the booking clerk can sell a ticket to each person and give the change. Otherwise print "NO".

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If the person has a 25 note, we don't need to account for change.
If the person has a 50 note, change given back has to be 25. (There has to be atleast one 25)
If the person has a 100 note, change given back can be either (25 + 50) or 3 25s. It is better to try the (25 + 50) option first because 50 can't be used for anything else.
And we need 25s to change 50s.

So we just have to keep track of number of 25s and 50s and check the conditions at each point in the line. We don't need to keep track of 100s.