Little Chris is bored during his physics lessons (too easy), so he has built a toy box to keep himself occupied.
The box is special, since it has the ability to change gravity.

There are n columns of toy cubes in the box arranged in a line. The i-th column contains ai cubes. 
At first, the gravity in the box is pulling the cubes downwards. When Chris switches the gravity, it begins to pull all the cubes to the right side of the box.
 The figure shows the initial and final configurations of the cubes in the box: the cubes that have changed their position are highlighted with orange.

http://codeforces.com/problemset/problem/405/A

Given the initial configuration of the toy cubes in the box, find the amounts of cubes in each of the n columns after the gravity switch!

Input
The first line of input contains an integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100), the number of the columns in the box. The next line contains n space-separated integer numbers. 
The i-th number ai (1 ≤ ai ≤ 100) denotes the number of cubes in the i-th column.

Output
Output n integer numbers separated by spaces, where the i-th number is the amount of cubes in the i-th column after the gravity switch.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------

A given block will fall to left wall, unless there is another block to break it's fall.
A block can stop another block's fall only if it is the same row.

The leftmost column will be the column with the maximum size.
Consider the block at the highest row of the longest column (longest, y) . Let's suppose there is no other block at it's row.
Then, There will be no block to break it's fall and it will occupy the same row on the leftmost column. (leftmost, y)
Let's suppose there are other blocks at the same row, but in other columns. In that case, the leftmost block of such a row(x,y)
 will occupy the same row of the leftmost column. (leftmost, y), {where x is to the left of longest}.
The same argument can be repeated for every block in the longest column.
After a while, the leftmost column will be of the same size as the longest column.

Now, after the leftmost column has been constructed, the leftmost column now acts like the 'wall' for the rest of the toy.
So, the second column from the left will be the largest column in the rest of the toy i.e., the second largest column.

Now, this column acts like the wall. And The third column will be the third largest and so on.

All we have to do is give a sorted list in ascending order from right to left!
A very interesting way to ask for a sorted list !