Vasily has a number a, which he wants to turn into a number b. For this purpose, he can do two types of operations:

multiply the current number by 2 (that is, replace the number x by 2·x);
append the digit 1 to the right of current number (that is, replace the number x by 10·x + 1).
You need to help Vasily to transform the number a into the number b using only the operations described above, or find that it is impossible.

Note that in this task you are not required to minimize the number of operations. It suffices to find any way to transform a into b.

Input
The first line contains two positive integers a and b (1 ≤ a < b ≤ 109) — the number which Vasily has and the number he wants to have.

Output
If there is no way to get b from a, print "NO" (without quotes).

Otherwise print three lines. On the first line print "YES" (without quotes). 
The second line should contain single integer k — the length of the transformation sequence.
On the third line print the sequence of transformations x1, x2, ..., xk, where:

x1 should be equal to a,
xk should be equal to b,
xi should be obtained from xi - 1 using any of two described operations (1 < i ≤ k).
If there are multiple answers, print any of them.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The following observations need to be made.

1. 2x is always even.
2. 10x + 1 is always odd.
3. An integer cannot be both even and odd simultaneously.
4. Performing either operation always leads to a bigger number. 

If we have a number b, then there is at most one number which could have transformed into b with the allowed operations.
If the number b is even, the b/2 is the only number that could have transformed into b.

If the number b is odd, then b' = (b-1)/10, is the only number that could have transformed into b. 10b' + 1 = b.
	However, is necessary to check if b' is an integer. I forgot to do this initially.
	For example, there is no integer x, which can transform itself to 15. 15 is odd. So no number becomes 15 by 2x.
	No integer x exists such that 10x + 1 = 15.

Call a number r the predecessor of a number t, if r can be transformed into t in a single step by the allowed operations.
It is easy to see that if t is even, then it has a unique predecessor. If t is odd, then it can have either 0 or 1 predecessor. In other words, predecessors, when existing, are unique. 
If we compute the list of predecessors b, b', b'', b''', ... , 1, then a can be transformed to b iff a lies on this list. 
Also, we know b > b' > b'' > b''' > ... > 1. So, we can stop searching when we get a predecessor which is not greater than a, because after it, all elements will be smaller than a.

So, we take b and build the list of it's predecessors until we either - 
1.  Get a predecessor which is no longer greater than a. And then check if the last predecessor obtained is a. If yes, display the path.
2.  Get a number which doesn't have a predecessor (like 15) and then stop.

To compute the predecessor, 
1. Check if the number is even. If it is, then n' = n/2 is the predecessor.
2. Check if the number is odd. If it is, then check if (n-1) is a multiple of 10. If it is, then the predecessor is n' = (n-1)/10
				If it isn't, then set 0 as the predecessor. This will meet our stopping criteria since the starting number a has to be at least 1, and 0 is less than 1. 

This problem would is very interesting because it would be exponential if we approached it from a.
a can become either 2a or 10a + 1. These two numbers can in turn become two other numbers.
The search space grows exponentially, and we would have to perform depth first search in every possible path until we get a number that isn't less than b and check if we have gotten b.
There are multiple paths to check.

This is a lot more complex. 

However, the same problem becomes much simpler if we just change our perspective with a simple insight and look at it from b to a. Now, there is only one path we need to check !