Dante is engaged in a fight with "The Savior". Before he can fight it with his sword, he needs to break its shields. He has two guns, Ebony and Ivory, 
each of them is able to perform any non-negative number of shots.

For every bullet that hits the shield, Ebony deals a units of damage while Ivory deals b units of damage. 
In order to break the shield Dante has to deal exactly c units of damage. Find out if this is possible.

Input
The first line of the input contains three integers a, b, c (1 ≤ a, b ≤ 100, 1 ≤ c ≤ 10 000) — the number of units of damage dealt by Ebony gun and Ivory gun, and 
the total number of damage required to break the shield, respectively.

Output
Print "Yes" (without quotes) if Dante can deal exactly c damage to the shield and "No" (without quotes) otherwise.

--------------------------------------------------------------

How many positive solutions are there to the Diophantine equation - ax + by = c ?

There is the number theory way and the brute force way. There are several ways of brute forcing. I did it with dynamic programming.

f(i) = true, if ax + by = i for non-negative x and y and false otherwise,

f(0) = true
i = 0 to c,
	if(f(i) == true)
		f(i + a) = f(i + b) = true

Answer is f(c)

Of course, this question is tied to Bezot's lemma and a solution exists if and only if, gcd(a,b) divides c. However, it allows x and y to be negative. I wasn't sure how
to check if only positive values of x and y are allowed.
