Quite recently a creative student Lesha had a lecture on trees. After the lecture Lesha was inspired and came up with the tree of his own which he called a k-tree.

A k-tree is an infinite rooted tree where:

each vertex has exactly k children;
each edge has some weight;
if we look at the edges that goes from some vertex to its children (exactly k edges), then their weights will equal 1, 2, 3, ..., k.
The picture below shows a part of a 3-tree.

As soon as Dima, a good friend of Lesha, found out about the tree, he immediately wondered: "How many paths of total weight n 
(the sum of all weights of the edges in the path) are there, starting from the root of a k-tree and also containing at least one edge of weight at least d?".
Help Dima find an answer to his question. As the number of ways can be rather large, print it modulo 1000000007 (10^9 + 7).

Input
A single line contains three space-separated integers: n, k and d (1 ≤ n, k ≤ 100; 1 ≤ d ≤ k).

Output
Print a single integer — the answer to the problem modulo 1000000007 (10^9 + 7).

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We set up a simple recurrence. 

f(i, j) be the number of paths which sum up to i. j is a boolean variable can be either 0 or 1.
	f(i, 0) is the number of paths which sum up to i where there is no edge of length at least d
	f(i, 1) is the number of paths whihc sum up to i, where there is at least one edge of length at least d.

f(i, 0) = f(i - 1, 0) + f(i - 2, 0) + ... + f(i - min{i, d-1}, 0),

Here, we start at a node and then select an edge of length 1, or of length 2, ... we can go on selecting edges till d-1 or till we have already reached the sum i.

f(i, 1) = f(i - 1, 1) + f(i -2, 1) + ... + f(i - (d-1), 1) + {f(i - d, 0) + f(i - d), 1) + f(i - d - 1, 0) + f(i - d - 1, 1) + ... f(i - min(i, k), 0) + f(i - min(i,k),1)}

Here, we start selecting edges. Till d-1, we just add f(i - edge, 1) to it.
		After we reach edge d, we have two options - f(i - d, 1) AND f(i - d, 0). Both options count since we can choose an edge of length d again 
			or we may not. Either way, they both contribute to the desired path combination.

To write this in a program. 

f(0, 0) = 0
f(0, 1) = 1

i = 1 to i = sum
	f(i, 0) = f(i, 1) = 1

	j = 1 to j = no_of_children & (i - j) >= 0

	if(j < d)
		f(i, 0) += f(i-j, 0)
		f(i, 1) += f(i-j, 1)
	if(j >=d)
		f(i, 1) += f(i - j, 0) //It need not be selected again 
		f(i, 1) += f(i - j, 1) //In case it is selected again

return f(n, 1)