Oleg the bank client checks share prices every day. There are n share prices he is interested in. 
Today he observed that each second exactly one of these prices decreases by k rubles (note that each second exactly one price changes, 
but at different seconds different prices can change). Prices can become negative. Oleg found this process interesting, and he asked Igor the financial analyst,
 what is the minimum time needed for all n prices to become equal, or it is impossible at all? Igor is busy right now, so he asked you to help Oleg.
 Can you answer this question?

Input
The first line contains two integers n and k (1 ≤ n ≤ 105, 1 ≤ k ≤ 10^9) — the number of share prices, and the amount of rubles some price decreases each second.

The second line contains n integers a1, a2, ..., an (1 ≤ ai ≤ 10^9) — the initial prices.

Output
Print the only line containing the minimum number of seconds needed for prices to become equal, of «-1» if it is impossible.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Notice that after all the reductions, all the shares have to be equal to the minimum price. 

If the shares are all equal after the minimum has been reduced by k at least once, then they shares would also have to be equal one day before the minimum is reduced too.

So, the answer is sum{ (a_i - min)/k }, 
		
	If a_i - min is not divisible by k, the answer is -1.

If any a_i cannot be reduced to min, it cannot be reduced to min - nk either, where n is any positive integer. 