Vasya lives in a round building, whose entrances are numbered sequentially by integers from 1 to n. Entrance n and entrance 1 are adjacent.

Today Vasya got bored and decided to take a walk in the yard. Vasya lives in entrance a and he decided that during his walk he will move around the house b entrances in 
the direction of increasing numbers (in this order entrance n should be followed by entrance 1). 
The negative value of b corresponds to moving |b| entrances in the order of decreasing numbers (in this order entrance 1 is followed by entrance n). 
If b = 0, then Vasya prefers to walk beside his entrance.

Illustration for n = 6, a = 2, b =  - 5.
Help Vasya to determine the number of the entrance, near which he will be at the end of his walk.

Input
The single line of the input contains three space-separated integers n, a and b (1 ≤ n ≤ 100, 1 ≤ a ≤ n,  - 100 ≤ b ≤ 100) — the number of entrances at Vasya's place, 
the number of his entrance and the length of his walk, respectively.

Output
Print a single integer k (1 ≤ k ≤ n) — the number of the entrance where Vasya will be at the end of his walk

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Simple modular arithmetic - 

(a + b) mod n

However, the house numbers start from 1. And the modular class start from 0. So, 

{(a - 1 + b) mod n } + 1

-1 is added to a so that the house starts from 0 and then 1 is added at the end to balance the answer out. 

To ensure the number is positive, if (a - 1 + b) is negative, then n is added to it to keep it positive. So, the final expression becomes - 

{ { {(a - 1 + b) mod n} + n }mod n} + 1

To increase readability, 
	end_house = (a - 1 + b) mod n + 1
	end_house += (end_house <= 0 ? n : 0)

