Furik loves math lessons very much, so he doesn't attend them, unlike Rubik. But now Furik wants to get a good mark for math. 
For that Ms. Ivanova, his math teacher, gave him a new task. Furik solved the task immediately. Can you?

You are given a system of equations:

a^2 + b = n, 
b^2 + a = m

You should count, how many there are pairs of integers (a, b) (0 ≤ a, b) which satisfy the system.

Input
A single line contains two integers n, m (1 ≤ n, m ≤ 1000) — the parameters of the system. The numbers on the line are separated by a space.

Output
On a single line print the answer to the problem.

--------------------------------------------------------------------

Clearly, a cannot be greater than m becuase a + b^2 = m, and b cannot be greater than n. 

Brute force and check all pairs (0<= a <= m, 0 <= b <= n) and check if the system is satisfied. Complexity - O(mn)