Harry Potter and He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named engaged in a fight to the death once again. This time they are located at opposite ends of the corridor of length l. 
Two opponents simultaneously charge a deadly spell in the enemy. We know that the impulse of Harry's magic spell flies at a speed of p meters per second, and the
 impulse of You-Know-Who's magic spell flies at a speed of q meters per second.

The impulses are moving through the corridor toward each other, and at the time of the collision they turn round and fly back to those who cast them without changing 
their original speeds. Then, as soon as the impulse gets back to it's caster, the wizard reflects it and sends again towards the enemy, 
without changing the original speed of the impulse.

Since Harry has perfectly mastered the basics of magic, he knows that after the second collision both impulses will disappear, and a powerful explosion will occur 
exactly in the place of their collision. However, the young wizard isn't good at math, so he asks you to calculate the distance from his position to the place of the 
second meeting of the spell impulses, provided that the opponents do not change positions during the whole fight.

Input
The first line of the input contains a single integer l (1 ≤ l ≤ 1 000) — the length of the corridor where the fight takes place.

The second line contains integer p, the third line contains integer q (1 ≤ p, q ≤ 500) — the speeds of magical impulses for Harry Potter and He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named,
 respectively.

Output
Print a single real number — the distance from the end of the corridor, where Harry is located, to the place of the second meeting of the spell impulses. 
Your answer will be considered correct if its absolute or relative error will not exceed 10 - 4.

Namely: let's assume that your answer equals a, and the answer of the jury is b. The checker program will consider your answer correct if .

------------------------------------------------------------------------

x = tp,
L - x = tq,

Where x is the distance from Harry where the collision occurs.

Therefore, L = t(p + q), this helps us find out how much time the first collision takes.

x = tp. 

Since the spells are always at the same speed, they take as much time to reach their casters as they did to reach the collision point i.e. simultaneously.
From here, the situation is exactly like the first time the spell was cast. 
This means that all collisions happen at exactly the same spot since the speeds remain constant.