Having written another programming contest, three Rabbits decided to grab some lunch. The coach gave the team exactly k time units for the lunch break.

The Rabbits have a list of n restaurants to lunch in: the i-th restaurant is characterized by two integers fi and ti. 
Value ti shows the time the Rabbits need to lunch in the i-th restaurant. 
If time ti exceeds the time k that the coach has given for the lunch break, then the Rabbits' joy from lunching in this restaurant will equal fi - (ti - k). 
Otherwise, the Rabbits get exactly fi units of joy.

Your task is to find the value of the maximum joy the Rabbits can get from the lunch, depending on the restaurant. The Rabbits must choose exactly one restaurant to lunch in.
 Note that the joy value isn't necessarily a positive value.

-----------------------------------------------

The joy is allowed to be negative. Other than that it's just an implementation problem. Be careful that the joy is allowed to be negative.

int main()
{
    int no_of_restaurants, time_limit;
    scanf("%d %d", &no_of_restaurants, &time_limit);

    const int NEGATIVE_INFINITY = -1e9;
    int maximum_joy = NEGATIVE_INFINITY;
    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_restaurants; i++)
    {
        int time_i, joy_i;
        scanf("%d %d", &joy_i, &time_i);

        if(time_i <= time_limit)
        {
            maximum_joy = max(maximum_joy, joy_i);
        }
        else
        {
            maximum_joy = max(maximum_joy, joy_i - (time_i - time_limit));
        }
    }

    printf("%d\n", maximum_joy);
    return 0;
}
