Sergey is testing a next-generation processor. Instead of bytes the processor works with memory cells consisting of n bits. 
These bits are numbered from 1 to n. An integer is stored in the cell in the following way: the least significant bit is stored in the first bit of the cell, 
the next significant bit is stored in the second bit, and so on; the most significant bit is stored in the n-th bit.

Now Sergey wants to test the following instruction: "add 1 to the value of the cell". As a result of the instruction, 
the integer that is written in the cell must be increased by one; if some of the most significant bits of the resulting number do not fit into the cell, 
they must be discarded.

Sergey wrote certain values ​​of the bits in the cell and is going to add one to its value. How many bits of the cell will change after the operation?

---------------------------------------------

Adding 1 to a binary numbers toggles all the bits up to and including the first 0 (from the LSB).
If there is no 0, it toggles all the bits and causes overflow.

--------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_bits;
    char initial_state[MAX_LENGTH];
    scanf("%d %s", &no_of_bits, initial_state);

    int first_zero_location = no_of_bits; //Assume there is no 0 so it will be outside the register at first
    for(int i = 0; i < no_of_bits; i++)
    {
        if(initial_state[i] == '0')
        {
            first_zero_location = i + 1; //0-indexed
            break;
        }
    }

    printf("%d\n", first_zero_location);
    return 0;
}