You have a description of a lever as string s. We'll represent the string length as record |s|, then the lever looks as a horizontal bar with weights of 
length |s| - 1 with exactly one pivot. We will assume that the bar is a segment on the Ox axis between points 0 and |s| - 1.

The decoding of the lever description is given below.

If the i-th character of the string equals "^", that means that at coordinate i there is the pivot under the bar.
If the i-th character of the string equals "=", that means that at coordinate i there is nothing lying on the bar.
If the i-th character of the string equals digit c (1-9), that means that at coordinate i there is a weight of mass c on the bar.
Your task is, given the lever description, print if it will be in balance or not. Assume that the bar doesn't weight anything. 
Assume that the bar initially is in balance then all weights are simultaneously put on it. After that the bar either tilts to the left, or tilts to the right, 
or is in balance.

--------------------------------------------------------

Different strategies were used to calculate the left moment and the right moment.

FIrst the right moment, because it's easier.

When we are in the right part, we have already seen the pivot. 
Keep track of the distance from the pivot. Whenever a weight is encountered, 
Right moment += distance*weight.

So for the left part, we don't know how far we are from the pivot.

Consider - 

a==b=^

The moment is 5a + 2b

If the pivot was in the second position, it would be a, 
Third it would be 2a, 
Fourth if would be 3a, 
Fifth it would be 4a + b

If the pivot is at position i, and the right moment is a. ma + b. mb + c. mc ... where ma, mb, mc denotes their multipliers, thne
when the pivot goes to position i + 1, it becomes a.(ma + 1) + b.(mb + 1) + c.(mc + 1) + ...

= a.ma + b.mb + c.mc + (a + b + c)

All the multipliers increase by 1. 

Till we encounter a pivot, we simply keep adding the sum of all weights encountered till that point to the left moment.

Got hit by an overflow error unexpectedly.

Of course, it is possible to solve this problem in 2 passes - Find the pivot position in the first pass, and then calculate the left moment 
how the right moment was calculated in the second pass (Because the position of the pivot is known now.)

-------------------------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    char lever[MAX_LENGTH];
    scanf("%s", lever);

    bool left = true, right = false;
    long long left_moment = 0, right_moment = 0, weights_till_here = 0;
    int distance_from_pivot;

    for(int i = 0; lever[i] != '\0'; i++)
    {
        if(lever[i] == '^')
        {
            left = false, right = true;
            distance_from_pivot = 0;
        }
        else
        {
            if(left)
            {
                if(lever[i] != '=')
                    weights_till_here += (lever[i] - '0');
                
                left_moment += weights_till_here;
            }
            else if(right)
            {
                distance_from_pivot++;

                if(lever[i] != '=')
                   right_moment += distance_from_pivot*(lever[i] - '0');
            }
        }
    }

    if(left_moment == right_moment)
        printf("balance\n");
    else
        printf(left_moment > right_moment ? "left\n" : "right\n");

    return 0;
}


