There exists an island called Arpa’s land, some beautiful girls live there, as ugly ones do.

Mehrdad wants to become minister of Arpa’s land. Arpa has prepared an exam. Exam has only one question, given n, print the last digit of 1378n.


Mehrdad has become quite confused and wants you to help him. Please help, although it's a naive cheat.

Input
The single line of input contains one integer n (0  ≤  n  ≤  10^9).

Output
Print single integer — the last digit of 1378^n.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

(10x + a)^n = a^n (mod 10) because every other term in the expansion of (10x + a)^n is a multiple of 10 i.e. = 0(mod 10).

1378^n = 8^n (mod 10)

the power of 8 are cyclic with period 4.

First check if n is 0, if it is, then the answer is 1.
	Otherwise the answer is 8^{n (mod 4)}} (mod 10)