The city park of IT City contains n east to west paths and n north to south paths. Each east to west path crosses each north to south path, so there are n^2 intersections.

The city funded purchase of five benches. To make it seems that there are many benches it was decided to place them on as many paths as possible. 
Obviously this requirement is satisfied by the following scheme: each bench is placed on a cross of paths and each path contains not more than one bench.

Help the park administration count the number of ways to place the benches.

Input
The only line of the input contains one integer n (5 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the number of east to west paths and north to south paths.

Output
Output one integer — the number of ways to place the benches.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

First choose any five columns. This can be done in nC5 ways. Now choose 5 rows and these points can be distributed among the 5 chosen columns
    nC5 x 5! = nP5. So, the total number of arrangements is nC5 x nP5. 

Division is carefully done to avoid overflow
In every consecutive n integers, there is an integer divisible by n. - n. (n - 1)/2 (n - 3)/3 (n - 4)/4 (n -5)/5 x n(n-1)(n-2)(n-3)(n-4)(n-5)
Division is not done at the last so the number is cut down before it overflows. 