Because of budget cuts one IT company established new non-financial reward system instead of bonuses.

Two kinds of actions are rewarded: fixing critical bugs and suggesting new interesting features. A man who fixed a critical bug gets "I fixed a critical bug" pennant 
on his table. A man who suggested a new interesting feature gets "I suggested a new feature" pennant on his table.

Because of the limited budget of the new reward system only 5 "I fixed a critical bug" pennants and 3 "I suggested a new feature" pennants were bought.

In order to use these pennants for a long time they were made challenge ones. When a man fixes a new critical bug one of the earlier awarded "I fixed a critical bug" pennants
 is passed on to his table. When a man suggests a new interesting feature one of the earlier awarded "I suggested a new feature" pennants is passed on to his table.

One man can have several pennants of one type and of course he can have pennants of both types on his table. There are n tables in the IT company. Find the number of ways to 
place the pennants on these tables given that each pennant is situated on one of the tables and each table is big enough to contain any number of pennants.

Input
The only line of the input contains one integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 500) — the number of tables in the IT company.

Output
Output one integer — the amount of ways to place the pennants on n tables.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

The number of way to distribute each kind of pendant is independent of each other. So, we find them individually and multiply them.

t_1 + t_2 + ... + t_n = 5 and
q_1 + q_2 + ... + q_n = 3.

The number of solutions is equal to the number of ways of placing n-1 barriers in between - X X X X X, 
For example, - X X X | X X, Here the first table got three and the last one got 2. The arrangement can be gotten by choosing the positions of the Xs in (n -1 + 5) positions.

So, the number of solutions = (n + 5 - 1)C 5 * (n + 3 - 1)C 3

While finding the value of the combination, an overflow may occur if we find the entire numerator - (n+4)(n+3)...n and then divide by 24.

So, we use the fact that in every n consecutive integers, there is a multiple of n and write it like (n+4)(n+3)/2 (n+2)/3 (n+1)/4 n/5.
This ensures that the integer division is always possible and there is no loss of precision. Among (n + 4) and (n + 3), one is a multiple of 2 since they are consecutive 
numbers. Among these two and (n + 2), one is a multiple of 3 and so on. The quotient is always an integer so we can take advantage of this to prevent overflow.