One way to create a task is to learn from math. You can generate some random math statement or modify some theorems to get something new and build a new task from that.

For example, there is a statement called the "Goldbach's conjecture". It says: "each even number no less than four can be expressed as the sum of two primes". 
Let's modify it. How about a statement like that: "each integer no less than 12 can be expressed as the sum of two composite numbers." Not like the Goldbach's conjecture, I can prove this theorem.

You are given an integer n no less than 12, express it as a sum of two composite numbers.

Input
The only line contains an integer n (12 ≤ n ≤ 10^6).

Output
Output two composite integers x and y (1 < x, y < n) such that x + y = n. If there are multiple solutions, you can output any of them.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Case 1 : n is even n = 2m,
		Subcase 1: m is even, then 2m = m + m, both of whom are even and composite
		Subcase 2: m is odd, then 2m = (m-1) + (m+1), both of which are even numbers.

Case 2: n is odd, n = 9 + (n - 9),
		(n - 9) is always even. And since n >=12, the odd numbers start from 13 in this range, so (n -9) is always greater than 2. 
		So, we always get an even composite number as (n - 9)