IT City company developing computer games invented a new way to reward its employees. After a new game release users start buying it actively, 
and the company tracks the number of sales with precision to each transaction. Every time when the next number of sales is divisible by all numbers from 2 to 10 
every developer of this game gets a small bonus.

A game designer Petya knows that the company is just about to release a new game that was partly developed by him. On the basis of his experience he predicts that n people 
will buy the game during the first month. Now Petya wants to determine how many times he will get the bonus. Help him to know it.

Input
The only line of the input contains one integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^18) — the prediction on the number of people who will buy the game.

Output
Output one integer showing how many numbers from 1 to n are divisible by all numbers from 2 to 10.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

To be divisible by every number from 1-10, it has to be divisible by 2^3, 3^2, 5, 7 i.e. 2520 - Any number divisible by 2520 can be divided by
every number from 1-10 because each i in between 1-10, has all it's prime factors in such a number.
    
Any number not divisible by 2520, will have atleast one number such that all it's prime factors aren't in that number. So, the condition is necessary and sufficient.