After you had helped George and Alex to move in the dorm, they went to help their friend Fedor play a new computer game «Call of Soldiers 3».

The game has (m + 1) players and n types of soldiers in total. Players «Call of Soldiers 3» are numbered form 1 to (m + 1). Types of soldiers are numbered from 0 to n - 1. 
Each player has an army. Army of the i-th player can be described by non-negative integer xi. 
Consider binary representation of xi: if the j-th bit of number xi equal to one, then the army of the i-th player has soldiers of the j-th type.

Fedor is the (m + 1)-th player of the game. He assume that two players can become friends if their armies differ in at most k types of soldiers 
(in other words, binary representations of the corresponding numbers differ in at most k bits). Help Fedor and count how many players can become his friends.

Input
The first line contains three integers n, m, k (1 ≤ k ≤ n ≤ 20; 1 ≤ m ≤ 1000).

The i-th of the next (m + 1) lines contains a single integer xi (1 ≤ xi ≤ 2n - 1), that describes the i-th player's army. We remind you that Fedor is the (m + 1)-th player.

Output
Print a single integer — the number of Fedor's potential friends.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The answer is the sum of all such i, that 
	 Population_count(Fedor_army^army[i]) <= k

^ represents the bitwise XOR operation

Popoulation count(x) is the number of 1s in the binary representation of x.

Population count can be counted in five steps by treating x as a 32 bit number by using the 'divide and conquer' method - first count no of 1s in every pair of bits,
then every 4 bits, than every 8 and every 16 and then 32. 