IT City company developing computer games decided to upgrade its way to reward its employees. Now it looks the following way. 
After a new game release users start buying it actively, and the company tracks the number of sales with precision to each transaction. 
Every time when the next number of sales is not divisible by any number from 2 to 10 every developer of this game gets a small bonus.

A game designer Petya knows that the company is just about to release a new game that was partly developed by him. On the basis of his experience he predicts that n people
 will buy the game during the first month. Now Petya wants to determine how many times he will get the bonus. Help him to know it.

Input
The only line of the input contains one integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^18) — the prediction on the number of people who will buy the game.

Output
Output one integer showing how many numbers from 1 to n are not divisible by any number from 2 to 10.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

It is sufficient to consider numbers which aren't divisible by any of the primes below 10. Any number not divisible by any of the primes below 10 isn't divisibly by any of
the other numbers either. 

The number of numbers divisible by the primes below 10 are given by the principle of inclusion and exclusion = (N/p_i - N/p_i.p_j + N/p_i.p_j._p_k - N/2.3.5.7)
Subtract this from N to get the required answer.