The numbers of all offices in the new building of the Tax Office of IT City will have lucky numbers.

Lucky number is a number that consists of digits 7 and 8 only. Find the maximum number of offices in the new building of the Tax Office given that a door-plate can 
hold a number not longer than n digits.

Input
The only line of input contains one integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 55) — the maximum length of a number that a door-plate can hold.

Output
Output one integer — the maximum number of offices, than can have unique lucky numbers not longer than n digits.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Each placeholder can hold 2 digits. So, for length n can have 2^n different numbers. 

Here, the answer is 2 + 2^2 + 2^3 + ... + 2^n = (1 + 2 + 2^2 + 2^3 + ... + 2^n) - 1 = 2^{n + 1} -1 -1 
			= 2^{n + 1} - 2

To do this, we simply shift 2 n times to the right. After n right shifts on 2, the 1 is at position, n + 1. 
This enables us to get the answer very quickly. (2LL << n) - 2