PolandBall is a young, clever Ball. He is interested in prime numbers. He has stated a following hypothesis: 
"There exists such a positive integer n that for each positive integer m number n·m + 1 is a prime number".

Unfortunately, PolandBall is not experienced yet and doesn't know that his hypothesis is incorrect. Could you prove it wrong? 
Write a program that finds a counterexample for any n.

Input
The only number in the input is n (1 ≤ n ≤ 1000) — number from the PolandBall's hypothesis.

Output
Output such m that n·m + 1 is not a prime number. Your answer will be considered correct if you output any suitable m such that 1 ≤ m ≤ 10^3.
 It is guaranteed the the answer exists.

------------------------------------------------

Here's what I first thought - 

Case 1 - N is odd, m = 1
	If n = 1 (mod 2), then 1.n + 1 = 1 + 1 = 2(mod 2) n+1 is always a multiple of 2 for odd n. Other than n = 2

There are three kinds of even numbers - 6a, 6a + 2, 6a + 4

Case 2 - N = 2(mod 6), m = 4

Case 3 - N = 4(mod 6), m = 2

I couldn't make it work for N = 0 (mod 6)

Then I saw the simple algebraic observation required in the editorial- n(n-2) + 1 = n^2 - 1, m = n -2, for everything greater than 2.
For 1 and 2, m=7 works.