n soldiers stand in a circle. For each soldier his height ai is known. 
A reconnaissance unit can be made of such two neighbouring soldiers, whose heights difference is minimal, i.e. |ai - aj| is minimal. 
So each of them will be less noticeable with the other. Output any pair of soldiers that can form a reconnaissance unit.

Input
The first line contains integer n (2 ≤ n ≤ 100) — amount of soldiers. Then follow the heights of the soldiers in their order in the circle — n space-separated integers 
a1, a2, ..., an (1 ≤ ai ≤ 1000). The soldier heights are given in clockwise or counterclockwise direction.

Output
Output two integers — indexes of neighbouring soldiers, who should form a reconnaissance unit. If there are many optimum solutions, output any of them. 
Remember, that the soldiers stand in a circle.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

First build a vector of the conescutive height difference given by C[i] = abs(H[i] - H[(i+1)%n])

Find the minimum value of C. Let it be at position j. 

This is the position of the first soldier. The second soldier stands at position 1 if j = n and (j + 1) otherwise