Greatest common divisor GCD(a, b) of two positive integers a and b is equal to the biggest integer d such that both integers a and b are divisible by d. There are many efficient algorithms to find greatest common divisor GCD(a, b), for example, Euclid algorithm.

Formally, find the biggest integer d, such that all integers a, a + 1, a + 2, ..., b are divisible by d. To make the problem even more complicated we allow a and b to be up to googol, 10100 — such number do not fit even in 64-bit integer type!

Input
The only line of the input contains two integers a and b (1 ≤ a ≤ b ≤ 10100).

Output
Output one integer — greatest common divisor of all integers from a to b inclusive.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If there are even two consecutive numbers, the answer is 1 because gcd(n, n+1) = gcd(n,1) = 1

And gcd(a, a+1, a+2, ... ,b) = gcd( gcd(a, a+1), .... , b) = gcd(1, ... , b) = 1

The only time the answer is not 1 is when a = b. Then the answer is a because gcd(a,a) = a

We don't need to use integer data types here. No arithmetic operations are required and we don't need to calculate the gcd.
So, we can treat the numbers as strings and strings of length 100 are handled very easily. The limits are easily managed.

We just need to compare the two strings and have an answer accordingly.