Petya loves lucky numbers. Everybody knows that lucky numbers are positive integers whose decimal representation contains only the lucky digits 4 and 7. For example, numbers 47, 744, 4 are lucky and 5, 17, 467 are not.

Petya calls a number almost lucky if it could be evenly divided by some lucky number. Help him find out if the given number n is almost lucky.

Input
The single line contains an integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 1000) — the number that needs to be checked.

Output
In the only line print "YES" (without the quotes), if number n is almost lucky. Otherwise, print "NO" (without the quotes).

-----------------------------

Simple. Write a function to check if a number is lucky - i.e. it has no digit other than 4 or 7.
Write another function to check if a number is almost lucky - go from 4 to n (because 1,2,3 aren't lucky numbers). Check if each i is lucky and if it divides n.

The bounds of the input are small enough to be managed by this brute source computation.