Petr wants to make a calendar for current month. For this purpose he draws a table in which columns correspond to weeks (a week is seven consequent days from Monday to Sunday), rows correspond to weekdays, and cells contain dates. For example, a calendar for January 2017 should look like on the picture:


Petr wants to know how many columns his table should have given the month and the weekday of the first date of that month? Assume that the year is non-leap.

.|2|9|16|23|30
.|3|10|17|24|31
.|4|11|18|25|.
.|5|12|19|26|.
.|6|13|20|27|.
.|7|14|21|28|.
1|8|15|22|29|.

Input
The only line contain two integers m and d (1 ≤ m ≤ 12, 1 ≤ d ≤ 7) — the number of month (January is the first month, December is the twelfth) and the weekday of the first date of this month (1 is Monday, 7 is Sunday).

Output
Print single integer: the number of columns the table should have.

-----------------------------------

The number of days after the first Monday of the given calendar = No of days in month + (starting day - 1)

1 is subtracted because there are (starting day - 1) free slots in the first column of the given month.

No. of columns = ceil(No of days in month + (starting day - 1) )