Devu is a renowned classical singer. He is invited to many big functions/festivals. Recently he was invited to "All World Classical Singing Festival". 
Other than Devu, comedian Churu was also invited.

Devu has provided organizers a list of the songs and required time for singing them. He will sing n songs, ith song will take ti minutes exactly.

The Comedian, Churu will crack jokes. All his jokes are of 5 minutes exactly.

People have mainly come to listen Devu. But you know that he needs rest of 10 minutes after each song. On the other hand, Churu being a very active person, 
doesn't need any rest.

You as one of the organizers should make an optimal sсhedule for the event. For some reasons you must follow the conditions:

The duration of the event must be no more than d minutes;
Devu must complete all his songs;
With satisfying the two previous conditions the number of jokes cracked by Churu should be as many as possible.
If it is not possible to find a way to conduct all the songs of the Devu, output -1. Otherwise find out maximum number of jokes that Churu can crack in the grand event.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The trick is to be greedy. Firstly, check if the minimum performance time is possible. 

The minimum performance time is the n songs and (n-1)*2 jokes in between each song. 

If it is possible, then the maximum jokes = (n-1)*2 + (total_time_available - minimum_performance_time)/(time_for_one_joke)

It needs to be rounded off to the nearest integer but this is automatically done in C.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

    maximum_jokes = -1
    for(i = 1; i <= no_of_songs; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &minutes_current_song);
        total_time_for_songs += minutes_current_song;
    }

    minimum_performance_time = total_time_for_songs + (no_of_songs - 1)*2*minutes_for_charu_joke;

    if(minimum_performance_time <= total_time_available)
    {
        maximum_jokes = (no_of_songs - 1)*2 + (total_time_available - minimum_performance_time)/(minutes_for_charu_joke);
    }