Tavak and Seyyed are good friends. Seyyed is very funny and he told Tavak to solve the following problem instead of longest-path.

You are given l and r. For all integers from l to r, inclusive, we wrote down all of their integer divisors except 1. 
Find the integer that we wrote down the maximum number of times.

Solve the problem to show that it's not a NP problem.

Input
The first line contains two integers l and r (2 ≤ l ≤ r ≤ 10^9).

Output
Print single integer, the integer that appears maximum number of times in the divisors.

If there are multiple answers, print any of them.

----------------------------------------------------------------------

If l = r, then the answer is l
Else, the answer is 2.

In any string of consecutive of m integers, there is a multiple of m. 
Take the interval in between l and r. 

Divide them into contiguous disjoint segments of length m.

The number of segments is (l - r)/m. The number of segments is maximised when the denominator is minimised i.e. when m = 2.