There is a fence in front of Polycarpus's home. The fence consists of n planks of the same width which go one after another from left to right. 
The height of the i-th plank is hi meters, distinct planks can have distinct heights.

Fence for n = 7 and h = [1, 2, 6, 1, 1, 7, 1]
Polycarpus has bought a posh piano and is thinking about how to get it into the house. 
In order to carry out his plan, he needs to take exactly k consecutive planks from the fence. 
Higher planks are harder to tear off the fence, so Polycarpus wants to find such k consecutive planks that the sum of their heights is minimal possible.

Write the program that finds the indexes of k consecutive planks with minimal total height. 
Pay attention, the fence is not around Polycarpus's home, it is in front of home (in other words, the fence isn't cyclic).

------------------------------------------------------

There is an array of integers. Find the minimum k-consecutive sum and return the starting index.

    for(i = 1; i <= no_of_planks; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &heights[i]);

        k_consecutive_sum += (i <= k ? heights[i] : heights[i] - heights[i - k]);

        if(i >= k && k_consecutive_sum <= minimum_k_consecutive_sum)
        {
            minimum_k_consecutive_sum = k_consecutive_sum;
            start_of_minimum_sum = (i - k + 1);
        }
    }

This returns the rightmost minimum k-consecutive sum.