User ainta has a stack of n red and blue balls. He can apply a certain operation which changes the colors of the balls inside the stack.

While the top ball inside the stack is red, pop the ball from the top of the stack.
Then replace the blue ball on the top with a red ball.
And finally push some blue balls to the stack until the stack has total of n balls inside.
 
If there are no blue balls inside the stack, ainta can't apply this operation. Given the initial state of the stack, ainta wants to know the maximum number of operations 
he can repeatedly apply.

Input
The first line contains an integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 50) — the number of balls inside the stack.

The second line contains a string s (|s| = n) describing the initial state of the stack. The i-th character of the string s denotes the color of the i-th ball
 (we'll number the balls from top to bottom of the stack). If the character is "R", the color is red. If the character is "B", the color is blue.

Output
Print the maximum number of operations ainta can repeatedly apply.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

I was looking for an invariant but the solution is stunning !

Think of the stack as a binary string with a blue ball representing 1 and red representing a 0.
Think of the stack as an integer.

What an operation does is change the suffix  100....0 to 011...1
It's quite easy to see that this is just decrementing by 1. (We get back the first number by adding 1 to the second.)

We cannot perform the operation anymore when it becomes 0. 

So, there are two ways of finding the value of n from the stack. This one uses multiplication and treats the number to be evaluated like a polynomial of degree n-1, 
with x = 2, using Horner's method.

    for(i = no_of_balls - 1; i >= 0; i--)
    {
        equivalent_number = (equivalent_number << 1) + (stack[i] == 'B' ? 1 : 0);
    }

The other method sets each bit individually using bitwise OR.

    for(i = 0; i < no_of_balls; i++)
        if(stack[i] == 'B')
            equivalent_number = equivalent_number| (1LL << i);