Alex doesn't like boredom. That's why whenever he gets bored, he comes up with games. One long winter evening he came up with a game and decided to play it.

Given a sequence a consisting of n integers. The player can make several steps. In a single step he can choose an element of the sequence (let's denote it ak) and delete it,
 at that all elements equal to ak + 1 and ak - 1 also must be deleted from the sequence. That step brings ak points to the player.

Alex is a perfectionist, so he decided to get as many points as possible. Help him.

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^5) that shows how many numbers are in Alex's sequence.

The second line contains n integers a1, a2, ..., an (1 ≤ ai ≤ 10^5).

Output
Print a single integer — the maximum number of points that Alex can earn.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Note - When a number x has been deleted, only that copy gets deleted but all occurences of x+1 and x-1 get deleted.
For example - x, x+1, x+1, x+1, x-1, x-1, x, x. If x is deleted, the array becomes - x, x.
Only 1 x can be deleted at a time. 

The following observation is required - 
The game goes on till all the numbers get deleted. 
If we delete a number - x, then all the other x's in the array can only be deleted by selection.
		Once we delete any one x, all x+1 and x-1 get deleted. So, they can't be deleted by deleting x+1 or x-1. 

Let f(i) be the greatest score possible where all numbers upto i are deleted.
	There are two options - Either we delete i by selecting it - f(i-2) + frequency[i]*i. 
	Or we delete it by selecting i-1 - f(i-1)

f(0) = 0
f(1) = frequency[1]

for i = 1 to 10^5
	f(i) = max{f(i-1), f(i-2) + i*frequency[i]}