Iahub got bored, so he invented a game to be played on paper.

He writes n integers a1, a2, ..., an. Each of those integers can be either 0 or 1. He's allowed to do exactly one move: he chooses two indices i and j (1 ≤ i ≤ j ≤ n) 
and flips all values ak for which their positions are in range [i, j] (that is i ≤ k ≤ j). Flip the value of x means to apply operation x = 1 - x.

The goal of the game is that after exactly one move to obtain the maximum number of ones. Write a program to solve the little game of Iahub.

Input
The first line of the input contains an integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100). In the second line of the input there are n integers: a1, a2, ..., an. 
It is guaranteed that each of those n values is either 0 or 1.

Output
Print an integer — the maximal number of 1s that can be obtained after exactly one move.

---------------------------------------------------------------

If a 0 is flipped, then the number of 1s increases by 1.
If a 1 is flipped, then the number of 1s increases by -1.

So, build a vector Gain, such that
Gain[i] = 1, if A[i] = 0,
Gain[i] = -1, if A[i] = 1

 Number of 1s = Number of 1s before a move + (Maximum Gain)

Maximum Gain can be gotten by finding the largest contiguous sum of the Gain array.

It can be found using Kandane's Algorithm, which can be proven inductively.

If there is only one element, then it is the largest contiguous subarray.

If we know the largest contiguous sum ending at index i, 
	then the largest contiuous sum ending at index (i +1) either includes this as a prefix or it doesn't. 

max_ending_here = max_so_far = A[0]

for i = 1 to (n-1)
max_ending_here = max{max_ending_here + A[i], A[i]}
max_so_far = max{max_ending_here, max_so_far}

max_so_far is the maximum of the greatest contiguous sums ending at each index i. 