We saw the little game Marmot made for Mole's lunch. Now it's Marmot's dinner time and, as we all know, Marmot eats flowers. 
At every dinner he eats some red and white flowers. Therefore a dinner can be represented as a sequence of several flowers, some of them white and some of them red.

But, for a dinner to be tasty, there is a rule: Marmot wants to eat white flowers only in groups of size k.

Now Marmot wonders in how many ways he can eat between a and b flowers. As the number of ways could be very large, print it modulo 1000000007 (10^9 + 7).

Input
Input contains several test cases.

The first line contains two integers t and k (1 ≤ t, k ≤ 10^5), where t represents the number of test cases.

The next t lines contain two integers ai and bi (1 ≤ ai ≤ bi ≤ 10^5), describing the i-th test.

Output
Print t lines to the standard output. The i-th line should contain the number of ways in which Marmot can eat between ai and bi flowers at dinner 
modulo 1000000007 (10^9 + 7).

----------------------------------------------------------------------------

Let f(n) represent the number of meals of length n.

The first flower can either be red or white. If the first flower is red, the remaining can be counted as f(n-1)
If the first flower is white, the next k-1 flowers are forced to be white, the remaining can be counted as f(n-k)

f(n) = f(n-1) + f(n-k) 

We build a table using this recursion formula.

Then build another vector sum, sum[i] = f(1) + f(2) + ... + f(i)

Now, the number of meals in between a and b is sum(b) - sum(a - 1). This is quicker than calculating the sum in the table every time. 

There were overflow issues. To avoid them, take mod with the required value while building the table itself. In this problem, Period = 1e9 + 7
f(i) = f(i)% Period, every time we calculate f(i)

sum(i) = sum(i)% Period, after every time sum(i) is calculated. (There will be overflow if Period isn't applied to calculated in f(i) but only calculated here.)

Lastly, answer = (sum(b) - sum(a+1) + Period)%Period,

Every sum(i) is less than Period, so their difference is guaranteed to be less than Period. So, why do we take mod Period here ? It looks unnecessary.
Because every sum(i) is stored % Period. It is possible for sum(b) < sum(a), In that case the answer would be negative. This is why we add Period and take modulus with it.