Vasya has the sequence consisting of n integers. Vasya consider the pair of integers x and y k-interesting, if their binary representation differs from each other exactly 
in k bits. For example, if k = 2, the pair of integers x = 5 and y = 3 is k-interesting, because their binary representation x=101 and y=011 differs exactly in two bits.

Vasya wants to know how many pairs of indexes (i, j) are in his sequence so that i < j and the pair of integers ai and aj is k-interesting. Your task is to help Vasya and 
determine this number.

Input
The first line contains two integers n and k (2 ≤ n ≤ 10^5, 0 ≤ k ≤ 14) — the number of integers in Vasya's sequence and the number of bits in which integers in k-interesting 
pair should differ.

The second line contains the sequence a1, a2, ..., an (0 ≤ ai ≤ 10^4), which Vasya has.

Output
Print the number of pairs (i, j) so that i < j and the pair of integers ai and aj is k-interesting.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Idea 1 - 

Go through the array. Compare every pair of elements. Perform XOR and find the no of 1s and check if it's equal to k. Increment count by 1.

--------------------------------------------------------

Idea 2 - 

In this problem, notice that the range of numbers is smaller than the size of the list. 10^4 vs 10^5
So, have an array of 10^4 length count[x], which holds the number of times x occurs. Read in the input - num. count[num]++.

Now, go through this array and compare every pair of elements. If count[x] > 0, then for all y > x, perform XOR and find it's population count.
If it is equal to k, then no_of_pairs = no_of_pairs + count[x]*count[y] (because every x, y pair forms a k-interesting pairs. count[x] ways to choose x, count[y] ways to 
									choose y, multiplicative principle of counting).

k = 0 is a special case, no_of_pairs = no_of_pairs + count[x](count[x] - 1)/2  {It is nC2}

Note - It was faster to build the count array simultaneously with the input than it was to go through the for loop again after the input was read and stored in an 
auxiliary array. 

It it still quadratic. Every pair is compared. But, now it is O(n^2) with n = 10^4 at most, rather than 10^5 - this takes advantage of the range being smaller than 
the size of the array.

Avoid overflow in multiplication. Either write (long long)count[x]count[y] or count[x]*1LL*count[y].

---------------------------------------------------------

Idea 3 - Instead of finding population count every single time individually, store it in a table.

Use the following recurence, if f(x) is the no of 1s in the binary form of x,

f(2x) = f(x), {String is left shifted once with 0 appended}
f(2x + 1) = f(x), {string is left shifted and 1 is appended}

It can be elegantly encapculated as one idea -

i from 1 to 2*RANGE
	f(i) = f(i/2) + i(mod 2)

It's important to note that the population count table should be twice as big as the RANGE. 

Let us suppose there is a binary number x - 10001, then we can XOR with 01110 to get 11111.
    We can XOR to numbers to get a number greater than either of the numbers. What is the greatest number we can get ?
    If x and y are binary numbers, and x > y, and the first 1 in the binary form of x is at position p (from the right),
    the greatest value of x XOR y is a number with all 1s from position p.
    So, x XOR y is always less than a 1 at position (p+1) and all 0s afterwards. So, 2*x is a loose upper bound.
    That is why we build a population count table till 2* RANGE instead of just RANGE

Storing it in a lookup table was substantially quicker than calling the function individually for every number. Time went from 234ms to 93 ms.
------------------------------------------------------------------- 