Kefa decided to make some money doing business on the Internet for exactly n days. He knows that on the i-th day (1 ≤ i ≤ n) he makes ai money. 
Kefa loves progress, that's why he wants to know the length of the maximum non-decreasing subsegment in sequence ai. 
Let us remind you that the subsegment of the sequence is its continuous fragment. A subsegment of numbers is called non-decreasing if all numbers in it follow in the 
non-decreasing order.

Help Kefa cope with this task!

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^5).

The second line contains n integers a1,  a2,  ...,  an (1 ≤ ai ≤ 10^9).

Output
Print a single integer — the length of the maximum non-decreasing subsegment of sequence a.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Code is linear complexity.

/If A[i] >= A[i-1], current streak increases, else a new streak begins.
        current_non_decreasing_streak = (  ( *(money_made + i) >= *(money_made + i -1) ) ? current_non_decreasing_streak+1 : 1 );
	
	longest_streak = max{current_streak, longest_streak}