Let's consider equation:

x2 + s(x)·x - n = 0, 
where x, n are positive integers, s(x) is the function, equal to the sum of digits of number x in the decimal number system.

You are given an integer n, find the smallest positive integer root of equation x, or else determine that there are no such roots.

Input
A single line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^18) — the equation parameter.

Please, do not use the %lld specifier to read or write 64-bit integers in С++. It is preferred to use cin, cout streams or the %I64d specifier.

Output
Print -1, if the equation doesn't have integer positive roots. Otherwise print such smallest integer x (x > 0), that the equation given in the statement holds.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------


This diophantine equation needs to be brute forced through. But, there is an elegant way to brute force through it. 

First, x^2 can be 10^18 at most, So, x can be at most 10^9. s(x) can be at most s(10^9 - 1) = 9*9 = 81

Let x^2 = n, then x^2 + s(x)*x > n, for sure. 

while(x^2 + 81*x >= n) //Use 81 as an upper bound instead of calling s(x) every time
	if(x^2 + s(x)*x == n)
		solution = x, break;
	
	x--

This is substantially better than going from 1 till root(n) and then checking if the equation is satisfied.


