ou are given sequence a1, a2, ..., an of integer numbers of length n. Your task is to find such subsequence that its sum is odd and maximum among all such subsequences.
 It's guaranteed that given sequence contains subsequence with odd sum.

Subsequence is a sequence that can be derived from another sequence by deleting some elements without changing the order of the remaining elements.

You should write a program which finds sum of the best subsequence.

Input
The first line contains integer number n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^5).

The second line contains n integer numbers a1, a2, ..., an ( - 10^4 ≤ ai ≤ 10^4). The sequence contains at least one subsequence with odd sum.

Output
Print sum of resulting subseqeuence.

---------------------------------------------------------------

Find the sum of all positive numbers. Keep track of the minimum |x| such that x is odd.
	If the sum we get is odd, return the sum. 
	Else - the minimum absolute odd number may be odd or even. 
		If it is positive, we delete it from the chosen subsequence. Sum becomes sum - x
		If it is negative, we add it to the subsequence, Sum becomes sum + x = sum - abs(x)
		In one line, we can write, sum = sum - abs(x)