A permutation is a sequence of integers p1, p2, ..., pn, consisting of n distinct positive integers, each of them doesn't exceed n. 
Let's denote the i-th element of permutation p as pi. We'll call number n the size of permutation p1, p2, ..., pn.

Nickolas adores permutations. He likes some permutations more than the others. He calls such permutations perfect. 
A perfect permutation is such permutation p that for any i (1 ≤ i ≤ n) (n is the permutation size) the following equations hold p(pi) = i and pi ≠ i. 
Nickolas asks you to print any perfect permutation of size n for the given n.

Input
A single line contains a single integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the permutation size.

Output
If a perfect permutation of size n doesn't exist, print a single integer -1. Otherwise print n distinct integers from 1 to n, p1, p2, ..., pn — permutation p, 
that is perfect. Separate printed numbers by whitespaces.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------

If p(i) = i, then it is clearly a perfect permutation. 

Since, this is not allowed, we swap adjacent values p(2k) = 2k+ 1 and p(2k + 1) = 2k
So, an answer is available for all even n.

Since, p(p(i)) = i, every time we change the value of p(i), we must also change the p(i) accordingly. Values have to get changed in pairs. Swapping adjacent values 
does the trick. 

However, if there are an odd number of elements, the last element will not have any number to get swapped with and will satisfy p(i) = i.
So, there is no perfect permutation for odd i.