You have n problems. You have estimated the difficulty of the i-th one as integer ci. 
Now you want to prepare a problemset for a contest, using some of the problems you've made.

A problemset for the contest must consist of at least two problems. You think that the total difficulty of the problems of the contest must be at least l and at most r. 
Also, you think that the difference between difficulties of the easiest and the hardest of the chosen problems must be at least x.

Find the number of ways to choose a problemset for the contest.

Input
The first line contains four integers n, l, r, x (1 ≤ n ≤ 15, 1 ≤ l ≤ r ≤ 10^9, 1 ≤ x ≤ 10^6) — the number of problems you have, 
the minimum and maximum value of total difficulty of the problemset and the minimum difference in difficulty between the hardest problem in the pack and the easiest one, 
respectively.

The second line contains n integers c1, c2, ..., cn (1 ≤ ci ≤ 10^6) — the difficulty of each problem.

Output
Print the number of ways to choose a suitable problemset for the contest.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

In a problem like this, we have to visit every single permutation of the the n problems and calculate the total, minimum, maximum difficulty and the number of problems 
in each arrangement. 

There is an elegant bijection which makes it easy for us to visit every permutation of n objects. 

We construct a bijection between every set chosen from n objects and a binary string of length n in the following way, 
	b[i] = 1, if the i-th object is chosen
	b[i] = 0, if the i-th object is not chosen

There are 2^n arrangements and binary strings of length n. 

We just iterate i from 0 to 2^{n-1} -1. Every value of i in this range corresponds to a different set chosen from these n problems.

for(i = 1; i < 2^n; i++) //i = 0 is skipped because when no problem is chosen, none of the constraints are met anyways.
	In the current arrangement, check if the j-th problem is chosen in the following way,
	If(i & 2^j != 0), it means problem j is chosen. 2^j corresponds to the arrangement when only problem j is chosen and nothing else. 
	                  if problem j is not chosen, then j-th bit of i will be 0. Otherwise it will be 1, resulting in a non-zero answer.

So, here's the answer - 

for(bitmask = 0; bitmask < 2^n; bitmask++) //2^n is 1 more than 2^{n-1} - 1 which is the string of n 1s
	current_min = 10^6 + 1, current_max = -1, total_difficulty = no_of_problems = 0
	//The values are initialised on each bitmask. The values of minimum and maximum are so set that the first problem selected becomes both min and max and from there
	//it's just the standard way of finding min and max. The min and max can't be set to c_0 like most arrays because c_0 may not be part of the chosen set.
	for(j = 0; j < no_of_problems; j++)
		if(bitmask & 2^j != 0)
			current_min = min{current_min, c_j}
			current_max = max{current_max, c_j}
			total_difficulty = total_difficulty + c_j
			no_of_problems++

//Check the conditions of current bitmask to see if this problem set passes the conditions and if it does increase count of legitimate problem sets by 1.  