Misha and Vanya have played several table tennis sets. Each set consists of several serves, each serve is won by one of the players, 
he receives one point and the loser receives nothing. Once one of the players scores exactly k points, the score is reset and a new set begins.

Across all the sets Misha scored a points in total, and Vanya scored b points. Given this information, determine the maximum number of sets they could have played, 
or that the situation is impossible.

Note that the game consisted of several complete sets.

Input
The first line contains three space-separated integers k, a and b (1 ≤ k ≤ 10^9, 0 ≤ a, b ≤ 10^9, a + b > 0).

Output
If the situation is impossible, print a single number -1. Otherwise, print the maximum possible number of sets.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Case 1: Both of them have won at least one set. (a > k && b > k) - Any configuration like this is allowed

Let the first set be (k, b mod k). Second set be (a mod k, k)

After that, multiple copies of (k, 0) follow till all of a's points have been reached and then multiple copies of (0, k) follow till all of b's points get covered.

Case 2: Only one of them has won sets. One of them has never won a set. 

	Let Misha be the one who has won all the sets. After each set, he gets exactly k points. Therefore, when the game ends, he must have (mk) points exactly.

	So, if (b < k, then a mod k has to be 0) and vice versa. 

Case 3: Neither of them have won a set.

In short, 
	if (a/k + b/k = 0) or (a < k and b (mod k) != 0) or (b < k and a (mod k) != 0),
		no of sets = -1

	else
		no of sets = a/k + b/k