The problem is:

You are given a lucky number n. Lucky numbers are the positive integers whose decimal representations contain only the lucky digits 4 and 7. 
For example, numbers 47, 744, 4 are lucky and 5, 17, 467 are not.

If we sort all lucky numbers in increasing order, what's the 1-based index of n?

Tavas is not as smart as SaDDas, so he asked you to do him a favor and solve this problem so he can have his headphones back.

Input
The first and only line of input contains a lucky number n (1 ≤ n ≤ 10^9).

Output
Print the index of n among all lucky numbers.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------

Construct a binary string in correspondence to the lucky number,
    b[0] = 0, 
    b[i + 1] = 0, if d[i] = 4 and 
    b[i + 1] = 1, if d[i] = 7
    4 corresponds with 01, 7 with 11, 44 with 001, 47 with 011 and so on.

    Where b[i] is the i-th letter of the binary string, and d[i] is the i-th letter of the decimal string.

    The binary string must be read from right to left.   
    The binary number we get is (reversed) always one more than the lexicographic number of the digit we have gotten since the first string is 2 and not 1.
    So, we subtract 1 at the end, after constructing a binary number from the given decimal string.

    We read the decimal string from right to left and then keep shifting each character to the left so that the rightmost character is at the leftmost end.
    This way we already get the reversed binary string, as required. 

	if(lucky_number[i] == '4')
        {
            index = (index << 1);
        }
        else if(lucky_number[i] == '7')
        {
            index = (index << 1) + 1;
        }

Note - The index can be atmost 2^{11} - 1, a string with 11 1s. So int is sufficient. 