Vasya has n days of vacations! So he decided to improve his IT skills and do sport. Vasya knows the following information about each of this n days: 
whether that gym opened and whether a contest was carried out in the Internet on that day. For the i-th day there are four options:

on this day the gym is closed and the contest is not carried out;
on this day the gym is closed and the contest is carried out;
on this day the gym is open and the contest is not carried out;
on this day the gym is open and the contest is carried out.
On each of days Vasya can either have a rest or write the contest (if it is carried out on this day), or do sport (if the gym is open on this day).

Find the minimum number of days on which Vasya will have a rest (it means, he will not do sport and write the contest at the same time). 
The only limitation that Vasya has — he does not want to do the same activity on two consecutive days: it means, he will not do sport on two consecutive days, 
and write the contest on two consecutive days.

Input
The first line contains a positive integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the number of days of Vasya's vacations.

The second line contains the sequence of integers a1, a2, ..., an (0 ≤ ai ≤ 3) separated by space, where:

ai equals 0, if on the i-th day of vacations the gym is closed and the contest is not carried out;
ai equals 1, if on the i-th day of vacations the gym is closed, but the contest is carried out;
ai equals 2, if on the i-th day of vacations the gym is open and the contest is not carried out;
ai equals 3, if on the i-th day of vacations the gym is open and the contest is carried out.
Output
Print the minimum possible number of days on which Vasya will have a rest. Remember that Vasya refuses:

to do sport on any two consecutive days,
to write the contest on any two consecutive days.

--------------------------------------------------------------------

We need to keep track of two entities - activity possible on current day, activity performed on previous day.

if(current_activity = 0)
	Rest has to be taken
if(current_activity = previous_activity = 1 or 2),
	then that means he is forced to rest on the current day.
	Because only one activity is possible on the current day and it was already performed on the previous day. 
else
	if(current_activity = 3),
		then if previous day was 1, do 2 today,
		      if previous day was 2, do 1 today,
		     if previous day was 3 or 0, do 3 today. 

	else
		do whatever activity is scheduled. There is no conflict.

for i = 1 ... n
	if(current = 0) or (current_activity = previous_activity = 1 or 2),
		previous = 0, //Rest taken today 
		rest ++ 
	else
		if(current = 3)
			previous = (previous < 3) ? (3 - current) : current
		else
			previous = current //Do whatever was planned