Vanya has a table consisting of 100 rows, each row contains 100 cells. The rows are numbered by integers from 1 to 100 from bottom to top, the columns are 
numbered from 1 to 100 from left to right.

In this table, Vanya chose n rectangles with sides that go along borders of squares (some rectangles probably occur multiple times). 
After that for each cell of the table he counted the number of rectangles it belongs to and wrote this number into it. Now he wants to find the sum of values in all 
cells of the table and as the table is too large, he asks you to help him find the result.

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the number of rectangles.

Each of the following n lines contains four integers x1, y1, x2, y2 (1 ≤ x1 ≤ x2 ≤ 100, 1 ≤ y1 ≤ y2 ≤ 100), where x1 and y1 are the number of the column and row of the 
lower left cell and x2 and y2 are the number of the column and row of the upper right cell of a rectangle.

Output
In a single line print the sum of all values in the cells of the table.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The number written on a cell increases every time a new rectangle is drawn including it. This question is equivalent to asking the number of cells covered by all rectangles.

The number of cells in 1 rectangle is (x2 - x1 + 1)(y2 - y1 + 1). We are adding 1 because the last cell starts at x2, and y2. As in that cell has a corner (x2 + 1, y2 +1).

We include that as well.

There isn't any point of storing the x and y coordinates of each rectangle so I have combined input with the processing for this question.