ittle boy Valera studies an algorithm of sorting an integer array. After studying the theory, he went on to the practical tasks. 
As a result, he wrote a program that sorts an array of n integers a1, a2, ..., an in the non-decreasing order. 
The pseudocode of the program, written by Valera, is given below. The input of the program gets number n and array a.


loop integer variable i from 1 to n - 1
    loop integer variable j from i to n - 1
        if (aj > aj + 1), then swap the values of elements aj and aj + 1

But Valera could have made a mistake, because he hasn't yet fully learned the sorting algorithm. 
If Valera made a mistake in his program, you need to give a counter-example that makes his program work improperly 
(that is, the example that makes the program sort the array not in the non-decreasing order). If such example for the given value of n doesn't exist, print -1.

---------------------------------

If n <= 2, any permuatation can be sorted like this.

Else, print them in descending order ...

n, n-1, n-2 ... 2, 1

After one pass ...

n-1, n-2, .... 2, 1, n

The second pass j starts from 2 and n-1 stays in the first position and j never touches it. 

In fact, it is sufficient to write - n, n- 1,( 1, 2, ... n-2 ) ... and give the rest of the list is sorted order.

The second largest integer is out of the range for the second pass so it will never be sorted.

--------------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_elements;
    scanf("%d", &no_of_elements);

    if(no_of_elements <= 2)
        printf("-1\n");
    else
        for(int i = no_of_elements; i >= 1; i--)
            printf("%d ", i);

    return 0;
}