The Little Elephant loves chess very much.

One day the Little Elephant and his friend decided to play chess. They've got the chess pieces but the board is a problem. 
They've got an 8 × 8 checkered board, each square is painted either black or white. 
The Little Elephant and his friend know that a proper chessboard doesn't have any side-adjacent cells with the same color and the upper left cell is white. 
To play chess, they want to make the board they have a proper chessboard. For that the friends can choose any row of the board and 
cyclically shift the cells of the chosen row, that is, put the last (rightmost) square on the first place in the row and shift the others one position to the right. 
You can run the described operation multiple times (or not run it at all).

For example, if the first line of the board looks like that "BBBBBBWW" 
(the white cells of the line are marked with character "W", the black cells are marked with character "B"), then after one cyclic shift it will look like that "WBBBBBBW".

Help the Little Elephant and his friend to find out whether they can use any number of the described operations to turn the board they have into a proper chessboard.

---------------------------------------------

Notice that the colour of adjacent squares is invariant on cyclic shifts.

In a chess board, each row has alternating colours ... If there's any row which has two consecutive squares of the same colour, a chess board can't be made.

Also, if two square in the end have the same colour ......WW , it may look like one cyclic shift will get rid of consecutive colours ... but it won't because in 
a chess board row the first and last square have different colours. 

Also, we need not seperately check if the first and last square match for every row ... because if all the squares in between them alternate, they are forced to be 
different.

---------------------------------------------


int main()
{
    const int no_of_rows = 8;
    bool all_rows_have_alternating_colours = true;

    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_rows; i++)
    {
        char row[NO_OF_COLUMNS + 2];
        scanf("%s", row);

        for(int square = 1; row[square] != '\0'; square++)
        {
            if(row[square] ==row[square - 1])
            {
                all_rows_have_alternating_colours = false;
            }
        }
    }

    printf(all_rows_have_alternating_colours ? "YES\n" : "NO\n");
    return 0;
}


