You have decided to watch the best moments of some movie. There are two buttons on your player:

Watch the current minute of the movie. By pressing this button, you watch the current minute of the movie and the player automatically 
proceeds to the next minute of the movie.
Skip exactly x minutes of the movie (x is some fixed positive integer). If the player is now at the t-th minute of the movie, then as a result of pressing this button, 
it proceeds to the minute (t + x).
Initially the movie is turned on in the player on the first minute, and you want to watch exactly n best moments of the movie, 
the i-th best moment starts at the li-th minute and ends at the ri-th minute (more formally, the i-th best moment consists of minutes: li, li + 1, ..., ri).

Determine, what is the minimum number of minutes of the movie you have to watch if you want to watch all the best moments?

------------------------------------------------------------

I thought I missed some things in this and didn't expect to get AC but I did !

Here's the strategy ... You know where the current minute it ... initially it is at 1. After each query, it goes to ri + 1.

Make as many jumps of length x as possible. Go as close to li as possible in steps of x and then watch as many minutes that are left.
This is the remainder with t ...

Because from the current minute ... li - current_minute = q. x + r, by the division algorithm .... 0 <= r < x

So, we reach q.x and from there we have to watch r minutes + the interval. 

------------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_interesting_portions, skip_step;
    scanf("%d %d", &no_of_interesting_portions, &skip_step);

    int current_minute = 1, no_of_watched_minutes = 0;
    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_interesting_portions; i++)
    {
        int beginning_i, end_i;
        scanf("%d %d", &beginning_i, &end_i);


        no_of_watched_minutes += (beginning_i - current_minute)%skip_step + (end_i - (beginning_i - 1));

        current_minute = end_i + 1;
    }

    printf("%d\n", no_of_watched_minutes);
    return 0;
}
