Vanya loves playing. He even has a special set of cards to play with. Each card has a single integer. The number on the card can be positive, negative and can even be equal 
to zero. The only limit is, the number on each card doesn't exceed x in the absolute value.

Natasha doesn't like when Vanya spends a long time playing, so she hid all of his cards. Vanya became sad and started looking for the cards but he only found n of them. 
Vanya loves the balance, so he wants the sum of all numbers on found cards equal to zero. On the other hand, he got very tired of looking for cards. 
Help the boy and say what is the minimum number of cards does he need to find to make the sum equal to zero?

You can assume that initially Vanya had infinitely many cards with each integer number from  - x to x.

--------------------------------------------------------

If the sum is 0, then no cards are required ... Otherwise be greedy ... Use as many cards of absolute value k, till the sum is less than k. After that use whatever card
the sum is.

In other words, it is ceil(sum/k) ... ceil = sum/k if it is a multiple of k, sum/k + 1 otherwise ... 

    int sum = 0;
    for(int i = 1; i <= number_of_cards; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &card_i);
        sum += card_i;
    }

    int no_of_cards_required = 0;
    sum = abs(sum);

    if(sum != 0)
        no_of_cards_required = sum/maximum + (sum%maximum != 0); //Ceil(sum/k)