The classic programming language of Bitland is Bit++. This language is so peculiar and complicated.

The language is that peculiar as it has exactly one variable, called x. Also, there are two operations:

Operation ++ increases the value of variable x by 1.
Operation -- decreases the value of variable x by 1.
A statement in language Bit++ is a sequence, consisting of exactly one operation and one variable x. 
The statement is written without spaces, that is, it can only contain characters "+", "-", "X". Executing a statement means applying the operation it contains.

A programme in Bit++ is a sequence of statements, each of them needs to be executed. Executing a programme means executing all the statements it contains.

You're given a programme in language Bit++. The initial value of x is 0. Execute the programme and find its final value 
(the value of the variable when this programme is executed).

Input
The first line contains a single integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 150) — the number of statements in the programme.

Next n lines contain a statement each. Each statement contains exactly one operation (++ or --) and exactly one variable x (denoted as letter «X»). 
Thus, there are no empty statements. The operation and the variable can be written in any order.

Output
Print a single integer — the final value of x.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------

Count the number of increment statements, and decrement statements.

Answer is no_of_increments - no_of_decrements