Someday, Drazil wanted to go on date with Varda. Drazil and Varda live on Cartesian plane. 
Drazil's home is located in point (0, 0) and Varda's home is located in point (a, b). In each step, he can move in a unit distance in horizontal or vertical direction.
 In other words, from position (x, y) he can go to positions (x + 1, y), (x - 1, y), (x, y + 1) or (x, y - 1).

Unfortunately, Drazil doesn't have sense of direction. So he randomly chooses the direction he will go to in each step.
 He may accidentally return back to his house during his travel. Drazil may even not notice that he has arrived to (a, b) and continue travelling.

Luckily, Drazil arrived to the position (a, b) successfully. Drazil said to Varda: "It took me exactly s steps to travel from my house to yours". 
But Varda is confused about his words, she is not sure that it is possible to get from (0, 0) to (a, b) in exactly s steps. Can you find out if it is possible for Varda?

Input
You are given three integers a, b, and s ( - 10^9 ≤ a, b ≤ 10^9, 1 ≤ s ≤ 2·10^9) in a single line.

Output
If you think Drazil made a mistake and it is impossible to take exactly s steps and get from his home to Varda's home, print "No" (without quotes).

Otherwise, print "Yes".

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. In a given move, either x or y changes by 1. To go from (0,0) to (a,b) it will take a minimum of (|a|+|b|) moves.
2. From a point (x,y), it is possible to return to (x,y) in an even number of moves only. 
	If an odd number of moves have been made, it means that one of the coordinates has been changed more times than the other. So, it isn't possible to return to (x,y).
	A simple example is (x,y) - (x+1, y) - (x,y) and variations of this. It is possible to return only after an even number of moves.

So,
1. If the number of moves, is less than the minimum distance, it is not possible.
2. Otherwise, if the number of moves = minimum distance + an even number, it is possible. i.e. (minimum_distance - no_of_moves) mod 2 = 0
3. In all other cases, it isn't possible.