Vasya likes everything infinite. Now he is studying the properties of a sequence s, 
such that its first element is equal to a (s1 = a), and the difference between any two neighbouring elements is equal to c (si - si - 1 = c).
 In particular, Vasya wonders if his favourite integer b appears in this sequence, that is, there exists a positive integer i, such that si = b. 
Of course, you are the person he asks for a help.

Input
The first line of the input contain three integers a, b and c ( - 10^9 ≤ a, b, c ≤ 10^9) — the first element of the sequence, 
Vasya's favorite number and the difference between any two neighbouring elements of the sequence, respectively.

Output
If b appears in the sequence s print "YES" (without quotes), otherwise print "NO" (without quotes).

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

An arithmetic progression is formed with starting term a, and common difference c.

If b falls in the progression, then a + nc = b, where n is a non-negative integer.
We have to check that (b-a) mod c = 0, and then that (b-a)/c >= 0,

The second condition is to prevent n from being negative. For example, the series given by (1, 5) should not accept -4. -4 is the '-1'th term.

Also, it is important to prevent division by 0, if c = 0, then b lies in the sequence iff a = b