Polycarp has interviewed Oleg and has written the interview down without punctuation marks and spaces to save time. 
Thus, the interview is now a string s consisting of n lowercase English letters.

There is a filler word ogo in Oleg's speech. All words that can be obtained from ogo by adding go several times to the end of it are also considered to be fillers. 
For example, the words ogo, ogogo, ogogogo are fillers, but the words go, og, ogog, ogogog and oggo are not fillers.

The fillers have maximal size, for example, for ogogoo speech we can't consider ogo a filler and goo as a normal phrase. We should consider ogogo as a filler here.

To print the interview, Polycarp has to replace each of the fillers with three asterisks.
 Note that a filler word is replaced with exactly three asterisks regardless of its length.

Polycarp has dealt with this problem in no time. Can you do the same? The clock is ticking!

Input
The first line contains a positive integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the length of the interview.

The second line contains the string s of length n, consisting of lowercase English letters.

Output
Print the interview text after the replacement of each of the fillers with "***". It is allowed for the substring "***" to have several consecutive occurences.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Comb through the interview string, one by one.
At each character, check if a filler begins. 
	If it does, find the length of the filler.
	Put three asterisks in the final string
	Continue combing through the interview string from position (current_position + filler_length)

	If it doesn't, copy the current character to the final string and go the the next character and repeat.

To check if there's a filler at position i,
	Check if 'ogo' is there. 
		If it isn't, return filler length as 0.

	If it is, then filler_length = 3, 
			Now, keep searching for secondary filler - 'go'
			If a secondary filler is found, filler_length = filler_length + 2, and search for another secondary filler
			
			If no more secondary fillers are found, return filler_length