There are n stones on the table in a row, each of them can be red, green or blue. 
Count the minimum number of stones to take from the table so that any two neighboring stones had different colors. 
Stones in a row are considered neighboring if there are no other stones between them.

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 50) — the number of stones on the table.

The next line contains string s, which represents the colors of the stones. We'll consider the stones in the row numbered from 1 to n from left to right. 
Then the i-th character s equals "R", if the i-th stone is red, "G", if it's green and "B", if it's blue.

Output
Print a single integer — the answer to the problem.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Go through the string linearly. 

For a character at position i,
	check from j = i + 1, if char[j] = char[i]. Keep incrementing j as long as you get a match, and all these stones must be added to the removed list.

Note - Although there are nested loops, the complexity is linear and not quaratic.

Because every time, the inner loop goes from j = i + 1 to j = x

i resumes from x. Since we have already removed those stones, it doesn't make sense to make i go through them again.