A triangular number is the number of dots in an equilateral triangle uniformly filled with dots. 
For example, three dots can be arranged in a triangle; thus three is a triangular number. 
The n-th triangular number is the number of dots in a triangle with n dots on a side. . 
You can learn more about these numbers from Wikipedia (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Triangular_number).

Your task is to find out if a given integer is a triangular number.

Input
The first line contains the single number n (1 ≤ n ≤ 500) — the given integer.

Output
If the given integer is a triangular number output YES, otherwise output NO.

---------------------------------------------------------

Find the first i, for which T(i) is not smaller than n.
Check if it is equal to n.