Makes solves problems on Decoforces and lots of other different online judges. Each problem is denoted by its difficulty — a positive integer number. 
Difficulties are measured the same across all the judges (the problem with difficulty d on Decoforces is as hard as the problem with difficulty d on any other judge).

Makes has chosen n problems to solve on Decoforces with difficulties a1, a2, ..., an. He can solve these problems in arbitrary order. 
Though he can solve problem i with difficulty ai only if he had already solved some problem with difficulty  (no matter on what online judge was it).

Before starting this chosen list of problems, Makes has already solved problems with maximum difficulty k.

With given conditions it's easy to see that Makes sometimes can't solve all the chosen problems, no matter what order he chooses. 
So he wants to solve some problems on other judges to finish solving problems from his list.

For every positive integer y there exist some problem with difficulty y on at least one judge besides Decoforces.

Makes can solve problems on any judge at any time, it isn't necessary to do problems from the chosen list one right after another.

Makes doesn't have too much free time, so he asked you to calculate the minimum number of problems he should solve on other judges 
in order to solve all the chosen problems from Decoforces.

----------------------------------------------

I first misunderstood the question I thought that he had to solve as less questions as possible on other judges so that he could solve all problems on the list.
But he is allowed to start, stop and practice only when required.

For example, if he can solve a problem of difficulty 2, and he has to solve problems of difficulty - 4, 8, 16, 64

If he must practice so that he can solve any of the questions from the list, he must practice 4 problems ... But going through the list, he must practice only one problem.

Ok so sort the problems by their difficulty since he must clearly start from the least difficult problem.

His initial range is 2k,

After that the range = max(2*difficulty[i], range)

If any difficulty is greater than his range, than solve problems till it is within the range, increment practice problems and double the range.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_problems, max_solved_difficulty;
    scanf("%d %d", &no_of_problems, &max_solved_difficulty);

    vector <int> difficulty(no_of_problems);
    for(int i = 0; i < no_of_problems; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &difficulty[i]);
    }

    sort(all(difficulty));

    int no_of_practice_problems_required = 0;
    int range = 2*max_solved_difficulty;

    for(int i = 0; i < no_of_problems; i++)
    {
        if(difficulty[i] > range)
        {
             while(difficulty[i] > range)
            {
                no_of_practice_problems_required++;

                range = range*2;
            }
        }

        range = max(2*difficulty[i], range);
    }

    printf("%d\n", no_of_practice_problems_required);
    return 0;
}