Polycarpus has an array, consisting of n integers a1, a2, ..., an. Polycarpus likes it when numbers in an array match. 
That's why he wants the array to have as many equal numbers as possible. For that Polycarpus performs the following operation multiple times:

he chooses two elements of the array ai, aj (i ≠ j);
he simultaneously increases number ai by 1 and decreases number aj by 1, that is, executes ai = ai + 1 and aj = aj - 1.
The given operation changes exactly two distinct array elements. Polycarpus can apply the described operation an infinite number of times.

Now he wants to know what maximum number of equal array elements he can get if he performs an arbitrary number of such operation. Help Polycarpus.

----------------------------------------

The first observation to make is that we fix one element (like a pivot) and then change all other elements, we can make n-1 elements equal to each other.

So, the answer is always at least n-1. When is the answer n ?

I couldn't get the answer for quite a while.

This is a transformation. Whenever there is a transformation, look for an invariant. What property remains the same as one increases and other decreases ?
I was trying to think of something related to gcd but I overlooked the most simple invariant - the sum !

The sum of array elements remains the same.

If all elements will be equal at the end, each element will be S/n at the end. 
That means the total sum must be a multiple of S.

-----------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_elements;
    scanf("%d", &no_of_elements);

    int sum = 0;
    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_elements; i++)
    {
        int element_i;
        scanf("%d", &element_i);

        sum += element_i;
    }

    printf("%d\n", sum%no_of_elements == 0 ? no_of_elements : no_of_elements - 1);
    return 0;
}


