"Hey, it's homework time" — thought Polycarpus and of course he started with his favourite subject, IT. 
Polycarpus managed to solve all tasks but for the last one in 20 minutes. However, as he failed to solve the last task after some considerable time, 
the boy asked you to help him.

The sequence of n integers is called a permutation if it contains all integers from 1 to n exactly once.

You are given an arbitrary sequence a1, a2, ..., an containing n integers. Each integer is not less than 1 and not greater than 5000. 
Determine what minimum number of elements Polycarpus needs to change to get a permutation (he should not delete or add numbers). 
In a single change he can modify any single sequence element (i. e. replace it with another integer).

------------------------------

Keep track of all elements that have occured and all elements that haven't occured yet. 
The number of operations used is equal to the number of elements that haven't occured yet. 

------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int n;
    scanf("%d", &n);

    const int limit = 5000;
    vector <int> is_present(limit + 1, false);
    for(int i = 1; i <= n; i++)
    {
        int element_i;
        scanf("%d", &element_i);

        is_present[element_i] = true;
    }

    int no_of_changes = 0;
    for(int i = 1; i <= n; i++)
        no_of_changes += (!is_present[i]);

    printf("%d\n", no_of_changes);
    return 0;
}