
------------------------Student Valera is an undergraduate student at the University. His end of term exams are approaching and he is to pass exactly n exams. 
Valera is a smart guy, so he will be able to pass any exam he takes on his first try. Besides, he can take several exams on one day, and in any order.

According to the schedule, a student can take the exam for the i-th subject on the day number ai. 
However, Valera has made an arrangement with each teacher and the teacher of the i-th subject allowed him to take an exam before the schedule time on day bi (bi < ai). 
Thus, Valera can take an exam for the i-th subject either on day ai, or on day bi. 
All the teachers put the record of the exam in the student's record book on the day of the actual exam and write down the date of the mark as number ai.

Valera believes that it would be rather strange if the entries in the record book did not go in the order of non-decreasing date. 
Therefore Valera asks you to help him. 
Find the minimum possible value of the day when Valera can take the final exam 
if he takes exams so that all the records in his record book go in the order of non-decreasing date.

----------------

First, sort the exams by the day. (First exam has to be taken first, second second, and so on).
Keep track of the day the last exam took place on. If the i-th exam took place on day l, the (i + 1)-th exam cannot take place before day l.

Choose the minimum option among a_i and b_i, which is greater than l.
Set that as the last day. 

------------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_exams;
    scanf("%d", &no_of_exams);

    vector < pair <int, int> > exam_day(no_of_exams + 1);
    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_exams; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d %d", &exam_day[i].first, &exam_day[i].second);
    }

    sort(all(exam_day));

    int last_day = 0;
    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_exams;i++)
    {
        int choice_1 = exam_day[i].first, choice_2 = exam_day[i].second;

        if(choice_1 >= last_day && choice_2 >= last_day)
            last_day = min(choice_1, choice_2);
        else if(choice_1 >= last_day)
            last_day = choice_1;
        else if(choice_2 >= last_day)
            last_day = choice_2;
    }

    printf("%d\n", last_day);
    return 0;
}