
Mahmoud and Ehab continue their adventures! As everybody in the evil land knows, Dr. Evil likes bipartite graphs, especially trees.

A tree is a connected acyclic graph. A bipartite graph is a graph, whose vertices can be partitioned into 2 sets in such a way, 
that for each edge (u, v) that belongs to the graph, u and v belong to different sets. You can find more formal definitions of a tree and 
a bipartite graph in the notes section below.

Dr. Evil gave Mahmoud and Ehab a tree consisting of n nodes and asked them to add edges to it in such a way, that the graph is still bipartite. 
Besides, after adding these edges the graph should be simple (doesn't contain loops or multiple edges). What is the maximum number of edges they can add?

A loop is an edge, which connects a node with itself. Graph doesn't contain multiple edges when for each pair of nodes there is no more than one edge between them. 
A cycle and a loop aren't the same 

---------------------------------------------------------------

To check bipartiteness of a graph, pick the root node and colour it black. COlour all of it's children white. Colour all of their children black.
Go on in this fashion untill all vertices are coloured. The graph is bipartite if there are no two vertices of the same colour which share an edge.

Now, if there are b black vertices, and w white vertices, the maximum number of connections is b*w.

The number of edges given is v - 1, v is the number of vertices. The difference between these two quantities is our answer.

Use DFS to colour the vertices of the graph. If a parent is coloured with one colour, colour it's children with the other colour.
Maintain a vector to check which node has already been visited.

-------------------------------------------

const int BLACK = 0, WHITE = 1, NO_OF_COLOURS = 2, MAX_VERTICES = 1e5 + 1;

vector <int> tree[MAX_VERTICES];
int visited[MAX_VERTICES] = {false};
int no_of_elements[NO_OF_COLOURS] = {0};

void dfs_and_colour(int v, int current_colour)
{
    int next_colour = (current_colour + 1)%2;

    if(!visited[v])
    {
        no_of_elements[current_colour]++;
        visited[v] = true;

        for(int i = 0; i < tree[v].size(); i++)
            dfs_and_colour(tree[v][i], next_colour);
    }
}

int main()
{
    int no_of_vertices;
    scanf("%d", &no_of_vertices);

    for(int edge = 1; edge <= no_of_vertices - 1; edge++)
    {
        int x, y;
        scanf("%d %d", &x, &y);

        tree[x].push_back(y);
        tree[y].push_back(x);
    }

    dfs_and_colour(1, BLACK);

    printf("%I64d\n", no_of_elements[BLACK]*1LL*no_of_elements[WHITE] - (no_of_vertices - 1));
    return 0;
}

