
In Berland recently a new collection of toys went on sale. This collection consists of 109 types of toys, numbered with integers from 1 to 109. 
A toy from the new collection of the i-th type costs i bourles.

Tania has managed to collect n different types of toys a1, a2, ..., an from the new collection. Today is Tanya's birthday, 
and her mother decided to spend no more than m bourles on the gift to the daughter. Tanya will choose several different types of toys from the new collection as a gift. 
Of course, she does not want to get a type of toy which she already has.

Tanya wants to have as many distinct types of toys in her collection as possible as the result. The new collection is too diverse, and Tanya is too little, 
so she asks you to help her in this.

---------------------------------------------

Be greedy. Buy the cheapest toy not available till the budget is exhausted.

--------------------------------------------

int main()
{
    int no_of_toys, money;
    scanf("%d %d", &no_of_toys, &money);

    set <int> toy_type;
    for(int i = 1; i <= no_of_toys; i++)
    {
        int toy_i;
        scanf("%d", &toy_i);

        toy_type.insert(toy_i);
    }

    vector <int> new_toys;
    for(int toy = 1; money >= toy; toy++)
    {
        if(toy_type.count(toy) == 0)
        {
            new_toys.push_back(toy);
            money -= toy;
        }
    }

    printf("%u\n", new_toys.size());
    for(int i = 0; i < new_toys.size(); i++)
        printf("%d ", new_toys[i]);

    return 0;
}