Sherlock has a new girlfriend (so unlike him!). Valentine's day is coming and he wants to gift her some jewelry.

He bought n pieces of jewelry. The i-th piece has price equal to i + 1, that is, the prices of the jewelry are 2, 3, 4, ... n + 1.

Watson gave Sherlock a challenge to color these jewelry pieces such that two pieces don't have the same color if the price of one piece is a prime divisor of the price of the other piece. Also, Watson asked him to minimize the number of different colors used.

Help Sherlock complete this trivial task.

Input
The only line contains single integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100000) — the number of jewelry pieces.

Output
The first line of output should contain a single integer k, the minimum number of colors that can be used to color the pieces of jewelry with the given constraints.

The next line should consist of n space-separated integers (between 1 and k) that specify the color of each piece in the order of increasing price.

If there are multiple ways to color the pieces using k colors, you can output any of them.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------

It's simpler than it appears. My idea was simple - Paint all the prime numbers red and all the composites blue.
No prime divides another so there's no conflict.
All of a given composite number's prime divisors are of a different colour. Still no conflict.

I overlooked the two small cases n = 1, 2. Where only one colour will be required since the two numbers will be {2} and {2,3}. 

The Sieve of Sunduram (with some optimizations) was used to construct an array is_prime.

is_prime[i] = 1, if i is prime
	    = 2, if i is composite.

And then the colours are simply printed on the screen. 