Iahub and his friend Floyd have started painting a wall. Iahub is painting the wall red and Floyd is painting it pink. You can consider the wall being made of a very large number of bricks, numbered 1, 2, 3 and so on.

Iahub has the following scheme of painting: he skips x - 1 consecutive bricks, then he paints the x-th one. That is, he'll paint bricks x, 2·x, 3·x and so on red. Similarly, Floyd skips y - 1 consecutive bricks, then he paints the y-th one. Hence he'll paint bricks y, 2·y, 3·y and so on pink.

After painting the wall all day, the boys observed that some bricks are painted both red and pink. Iahub has a lucky number a and Floyd has a lucky number b. Boys wonder how many bricks numbered no less than a and no greater than b are painted both red and pink. This is exactly your task: compute and print the answer to the question.

Input
The input will have a single line containing four integers in this order: x, y, a, b. (1 ≤ x, y ≤ 1000, 1 ≤ a, b ≤ 2·109, a ≤ b).

Output
Output a single integer — the number of bricks numbered no less than a and no greater than b that are painted both red and pink.

------------------------------------------------------------

The first brick painted both pink and red is the lcm(x,y), and we know lcm(x,y)gcd(x,y) = xy

The answer is b/lcm - (a-1)/lcm

Not less than a doesn't include a so a doesn't count.