Every summer Vitya comes to visit his grandmother in the countryside. This summer, he got a huge wart. Every grandma knows that one should treat warts when the moon goes down.
 Thus, Vitya has to catch the moment when the moon is down.

Moon cycle lasts 30 days. 
The size of the visible part of the moon (in Vitya's units) for each day is
 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, and then cycle repeats, thus after the second 1 again goes 0.

As there is no internet in the countryside, Vitya has been watching the moon for n consecutive days and for each of these days he wrote down the size of the visible part of the moon. Help him find out whether the moon will be up or down next day, or this cannot be determined by the data he has.

Input
The first line of the input contains a single integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 92) — the number of consecutive days Vitya was watching the size of the visible part of the moon.

The second line contains n integers ai (0 ≤ ai ≤ 15) — Vitya's records.

It's guaranteed that the input data is consistent.

Output
If Vitya can be sure that the size of visible part of the moon on day n + 1 will be less than the size of the visible part on day n, 
then print "DOWN" at the only line of the output. If he might be sure that the size of the visible part will increase, then print "UP". 
If it's impossible to determine what exactly will happen with the moon, print -1.

Examples
input
5
3 4 5 6 7
output
UP
input
7
12 13 14 15 14 13 12
output
DOWN
input
1
8
output
-1
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

The following insight is required - if the last observation is 15, the moon has to go down. If the last observation is 0, moon has to go up.

Unless it is 15 or 0, one observation is insufficient to answer.

The last two observations are required.
If the last two observations are in ascending order, moon goes up. (Unless the last is 15)
If they're in descending order, moon goes down. (Unless the last it 0.)